***Subtitles by Ardarvin & Mayumi***
Let's move on to the next check.
Here is the third check.
Check 3: String Octet.
Our octet is scored for four violins, and two violas and two cellos.
Up to now, the highest total value of instruments on this show was...
79.5 billion yen, featured last year.
This time, we're going beyond that.
We want you to savor an even more miraculous sound.
The eight instruments in this octet have a record-breaking total value of 10.24 billion yen.
So we've finally broken the 10-billion-yen mark.
That's incredible.
An absolutely staggering amount.
Check 3: String Octet
This time, Japan Violin, a specialist in top-class string instruments has prepared...
Eight instruments, every single one a world-class masterpiece.
Two violas:
a Domenico Montagnana, 150 million yen,
and a Lorenzo Storioni, 300 million yen.
Cello: the ''Spirito Sorsana'', 90 million yen,
and a Matteo Goffriller, 700 million yen.
Four violins:
first, a Guarneri del Gesù ''Prince Doria'', 2.3 billion yen.
Among the roughly 200 surviving examples in the world, this one is especially prized.
The remaining three are all Stradivarius violins.
A 1727 Stradivarius, 1.8 billion yen.
An important work from Stradivari's highly refined late period.
The Stradivarius ''Kreisler'', 2.4 billion yen.
A rare masterpiece once owned by 20th-century virtuoso Fritz Kreisler, famed for its mature, rounded tone.
And after three years of negotiation, it is finally being shown in Japan for the first time.
The Stradivarius ''Corbett''.
It is worth a program-record...
2.5 billion yen.
Together, these eight instruments produce a sound worth 10.24 billion yen.
And what you'll be comparing that to is...
Instruments used by people who play music as a hobby.
Their total value: 10 million yen.
Even so...
It's still 10 million yen.
That's right.
Both the correct and incorrect answers will be played...
...by world-class performers active on the international stage.
Now we'll announce the representatives.
From Team 83 Wins in a Row...
Mr. GACKT.
We're counting on you.
From Team Dendou Emiko...
Ms. Emiko Uemura.
Thank you for taking part.
And these are the rest of the representatives.
A price difference of a thousand times...
There's no way you could get this wrong, right?
All right, representatives, please head to the standby room.
Off you go.
The third check.
What is going to happen?
In the standby room...
They're treated according to their rank.
They treat regular talent badly
usually it's not that bad.
When acting, behind the scenes we use paper cups
Bon appetite...
For this check, several people will listen at the same time.
First, these four pairs will take the test.
Live performances in the studio by top-level musicians.
Everyone at home, please listen along with them.
First, octet A.
Now octet B.
Did you hear the 10.24 billion yen difference?
Who thinks it's A?
So everyone else thinks B?
How do you think it sounded?
Both the low and high notes sounded beautiful
Hiromi also picked B?
I also was listening to the low notes
I thought...
they were very clear
Tendo-san also B?
I think I'll pick A
With the 10.24-billion-yen set,
the sound of the bow hitting the strings, the way it rings out...
well...  you know...
is on a whole different level from newer instruments. The resonance really soars.
I see, yes.
Can Ryoma Takeuchi stay first-class?
Here we go.
For question three, you answered B.
Now we'll see if that lines up or not.
Mr. Takeuchi, how are you feeling?
I mean, we get to hear instruments worth 10.24 billion yen, right?
That's right.
I'm actually starting to have fun with this.
You're really enjoying yourself.
In the end, it's an insanely rare sound, isn't it?
Exactly.
So I can just ride that emotion...
and pick the right instruments.
So for you this one's easy, then?
Ridiculously easy.
Super easy.
All right, the answer he gave is...
B.
They match.
To me, B...
...sounded more beautiful.
And also, you know...
When it went up into the high notes...
How should I put it...
The ''flavor'' of the sound, I guess?
What is with the way this guy talks? It's annoying.
It's like he's drunk on red wine or something.
He really had quite a bit to drink, you know.
So that great feeling was from the red wine, huh?
Takeuchi goes all in and picks B.
Now, a top-tier artist steps up:
here comes Koda Kumi.
Hmm...I feel like...
(Hiromi-san picked B)
In my 25 years as an artist,
you know, obviously,
I’ve worked with string sections a lot,
and performed with them so many times.
there's no way I will pick the wrong answer
If an actor or a comedian gets this wrong, I think that can’t be helped.
But if a musician misses this, that’s basically grounds for...
retirement.
Retirement!
Whoa, don’t say that!
So what’s the answer she gave, with her career on the line?
The correct answer is B!
They matched
What struck me was just how rich and thick the cello sound was,
and the violins really rang out too.
The sound seemed to soar upward and resonate,
so it almost made the piece itself feel different to me.
This could be retirement
By the way, Go Hiromi, who appeared on the New Year 2022 Kakuzuke Check,
got this one wrong.
Hiromi-san, you are on thin ice with this one.
You’d practically be forced into retirement if you missed it.
With her career at stake, she chose B.
There are battles you simply can’t afford to lose.
I'm relieved
(relieved)
And now, the very ordinary Kansai talent:
Emiko Kaminuma.
Here we go.
I’m really glad I got to do this segment this time.
If Tendo Yoshimi were to get this wrong,
it wouldn’t be a laughing matter.
Because this is about music.
I’ll go with the one that made my inner body tremble.
The one that shook her cells was...
On this you agreed with Tendo-san?
The impact was just on another level.
It hit me right in the gut with a deep boom.
No matter how I think about it, A shook me more.
My heart was trembling.
Emi-chan, with her cells and her heart both quivering,
chooses A, where no one else has gone.
No one.
Nobody.
Going in all alone...
Oh, wow, wow.
Oh man, this is exactly the kind of thing that makes you super anxious.
This is a crucial check for how things go from here.
Is the correct answer A or B?
A total value of the 8 professional instruments is 10.24-billion-yen
Is it A, or is it B?
Now it’s time to reveal the correct answer to everyone in the studio.
All right, the correct answer is...
A.
Just you got the right answer
That's right. Astushi please pick correctly!
A made me tremble
She protects the reputation of Kansai talent
Sorry to announce this sad news on New Years...
Koda Kumi will retire today
We must not forget:
Go Hiromi got it wrong again.
Breaking news! Hiromi Go retires!
These guys also absolutely can’t afford to miss it as artists.
The three from Kis-My-Ft2
Please!
Go with A.
The price gap is massive, isn’t it?
So you’d think you’d be able to feel something.
Do you feel it!?
..as an artist.
What do these artists feel? Now in their 15th year?
Ready, set...
Oh no!
A lot of them picked B.
This is bad.
Why, why?
I honestly couldn’t tell which one was better,
but we had that low sound coming from behind us, right?
The cello, yeah.
From the way that sound distorted, I thought this one might have more history to it.
Being 2-to-1 is a disadvantage, you know.
Fukaya-san, I’m counting on you.
Don't give up!
B felt more cohesive overall.
That’s why, for me, A actually felt like
it had more character, like it carried more history.
Yes, yes, yes!
Because I really couldn’t tell.
'A' was more dull, you know? Not so sharp.
Not sharp?
Oh, shut up!
Still, I think it’s B.
I’m going with B. Definitely B.
Wait! Oh no!
B.
Watching it like this really starts to piss me off
Kis-My, who are top class, absolutely perfect...
...head on over to the wrong-answer B room, where all the other hopeless artists are waiting.
Kuri's here!
Yes, he's here! Alright!
Team Artist!
(worried but correct)
Kaminuma-san fainted!
Oh she fell down... are you ok?
I'm going to use all this space
She looks like she's sitting at home
Next up...
..these 4 teams
Gakt has to participate in all questions himself
He has lots of pressure
Now, please enjoy the sound of this 10.24-billion-yen instruments
To keep his winning streak alive, we turn to GACKT.
Here we go.
I wonder which one GACKT picked.
Lord GACKT, aiming for his 84th straight win,
how did he work out the answer?
I focused on how much of its character really stood out,
and also,
the strength of the sound right in the Strad's key range,
around 2000 to 6000 Hz,
and the quality of it's attack...
(is he serious?)
...and sustain.
You have to zero in on that balance alone.
If you just listen to the performance and pick the one that sounded better as a performance,
I think you will definitely get it wrong.
Which one did he choose?
Did Lord GACKT ignore the performance and still manage to pick the right one?
(He can see the other rooms on the monitor)...
Yeah, figured as much.
But it must be nice having so many people.
Yeah, being in a big group.
You can actually talk it over.
On your own you do feel a bit insecure.
Yeah, exactly.
This one is tough.
Can he hang on to his top-tier status?
Team Yoshimoto, Atsushi Tamura.
Yeah, I mean, I've been in a band for 20 years too,
That's right.
I've heard all kinds of sounds,
so I think I can tell the difference.
There’s no way our great senior can afford to get this wrong.
The correct answer is...
B.
We’ve got another mismatch here.
Give me a break!
I closed my eyes,
and just gave myself over to every single sound.
And B was the one that made me smile more.
When you feel that warm, gentle quality,
when a sound has that warmth to it,
you just end up smiling.
What on earth are you talking about?
He may have been all smiles, but that top-star aura didn’t help him: off to the wrong-answer B room.
Whoa, seriously?
Kaminuma!
Kaminuma just collapsed!
(Confident but wrong)
Emi-chan is...
We don't know yet
We still don’t know for sure, though.
Ordinary actors: Kimura Tae and Mitsuomi Takahashi.
Alright, we’re up.
We’re counting on you.
When you’re talking 10.2 billion yen, I feel like you don’t hear it anymore, you practically see the sound.
The sound itself.
Hamada-san silent laugh!
Silent!
Did they manage to 'see' the 10.2-billion-yen sound?
What did they answer?
Ready, set...
No split but wrong!
Why?!
They don't need to argue
From the very first note they were completely different.
A felt a bit heavier in terms of weight,
and B felt lighter
Kimura, once we wrap this shoot,
you better go see an ear doctor.
That’s fair, right?
Yeah, fair enough.
For the first time in this studio, we’ve got second-rate celebrities on our hands.
They agreed completely and were full of confidence, only to plummet straight into second-rate status.
Head to the B room, the bug trap for bad ears.
Thank God!
I’m so happy.
Huh?
They’re going to B again
(Reminded of her loneliness from the Wine check)
This is kinda frustrating.
It’s really frustrating.
(Gackt killing time with selfie)
When listening to the sound together, people probably pick ______
First time performing on the Kouhaku Song Festival,
just your average idols.
Alright, this is the last team
Go for it, Fruits Chuck!
(old people call a zipper a "chuck")
We’re 'Zipper'.
It's 'zipper'.
Matsukare actually graduated from a music college.
Matsukare did?
You went to a music college, Matsukare?
You've never told anyone that before.
I mean, I also did classical piano for ten years.
Seriously?
Then it’s hard to decide whose opinion to go with.
Leave it to me too, I think I’ve got a pretty good ear.
She really does have a good ear, so we’re fine.
Oh, this is where you shine?
You haven't done anything yet!
Just trust in my one weapon: my great ear, and go all in.
Because my ears are sharp.
At least wanting to keep regular talent level...
What’s their answer?
Ready, and...
Wait!
Luna, luna, luna...
To me, B sounded tighter and not so light or flimsy.
Because she has a good ear.
Yui-chan is betting everything on that one strength.
Then we’ll go with B.
We choose B.
They went to B!
B.
That was fast.
From today on, why don’t we just call it Fruit Chuck?
I liked 'zipper' better.
It actually has a proper meaning, you know.
From today, 'Fruit Chuck' is officially wrong too.
And with that, lonely little Emiko Kaminuma who waited all by herself has won it all.
Ready, and...
Whoa!
For real?
(the only winner)
Huh?
It’s just Kaminuma-san, all by herself.
Yes I'm by myself.
She really did win it all on her own.
Emiko Kaminuma: a miraculous solo victory!
Coming up: don’t miss Emi-chan crying tears of joy.
The crossroads of fate: time for the results.
All right, here we go.
I'm going to reveal the answer!
Please, go ahead.
I’m scared, I’m scared...
The right answer is...
(futile prayers)
(she will be thrilled!)
Congratulations!
You won by yourself
YA TA!
I'm so happy!
Seriously?
No way
Unexpectedly
happy hug
I’ve never been this happy in my whole life.
Yes!
I did it!
I’m so happy.
Nothing could make me happier ... at this age
Kaminuma-san is in tears.
Now everyone, we have some sad news.
This year, Kumi Koda will be retiring.
Stop it!
Seriously?
A huge upset in the 8 string orchestra
Did Lord Gackt manage to pick the correct answer, A?
At the crossroads of fate: Gackt’s answer revealed.
All right, I’m sure GAKU-chan is in this one too.
Now, I’ll open the door to the correct room.
Shaaa!
Brilliant—84 wins in a row!
That’s insane.
Even I was a little unsure.
Each part was so strong on its own that together it sounded kind of rough.
But if you listen to each element, A is overwhelmingly stronger.
He somehow cleared the question he was worried about.
The unstoppable Lord Gackt’s winning streak is now at 84.
With this, Lord Gackt is the only top-tier celebrity left.
Why does it always end up like this?
Try a little harder
Our two correct answerers have returned.
84straight wins, and Kaminuma-sama’s three-years-in-the-making revenge is complete.
Excellent!
Impressive, impressive, truly impressive.
Now, everyone who got it wrong, please proceed to pay your respects.
Our wrong answerers will enter to a performance by staff who has never taken a single violin lesson.
Wow, what an incredible sound...
Oh man, what is this?
Our wrong answerers have returned.
Everyone is back.
We were totally confident.
Atsushi!
Please disband your band immediately.
Uh, this is Koda-san, right?
I’m Koda
Nice to be working with you.
So from today you will...
No, no, no, that was staff’s twisting our arm
No we didn't.
Fruit chuck.
You were really full of confidence too, though.
I learned a lot from that.
All right, let’s move on. Time for the next check.
Here is the fourth check.
Check 4: Michelin Chef
The Michelin Guide is globally renowned and trusted for rating restaurants.
This time, you’ll have to identify the chef from a restaurant
that has held one Michelin star for eight years in a row.
This is the Michelin-starred chef is...
Chef Ippei Matsumoto of L’ape in Nihonbashi, Tokyo.
Check 4: Michelin Chef.
L’ape, a famous restaurant in Nihonbashi, Tokyo, with one Michelin star for eight straight years.
Owner-chef Ippei Matsumoto specializes in modern French cuisine.
He blends classic French cooking with seasonal Japanese ingredients.
His seasonal menus bring out the full natural flavor of each ingredient.
This challenge features two Western favorites: beef stew
and doria.
Chef Matsumoto, with his one Michelin star, prepared the dishes for us.
And here are the people we’ll be comparing him with.
The Sato brothers from Ox in Nippori, Tokyo.
Chef Tadao Sato and his younger brother, Chef Eiji.
Their signature dish is their mixed-fry set meal.
That looks delicious.
Ox is a long-standing Western-style restaurant that has been beloved by locals for over 50 years.
The ones who have kept that flavor alive are
the elder brother, 82-year-old Chef Tadao,
and his 73-year-old younger brother, Chef Eiji.
For reference, we had the two brothers taste the correct Michelin dishes beforehand.
delicious
excellent!
It's good but our food is better
Agreed
We can do it
By the way, as for the doria,
it’s not actually on their menu,
so they made doria for the first time since the restaurant opened.
Now then, everyone, this particular challenge
is a three-way choice: A, B, or C.
So unlike usual, this check has A, B, and also C.
And one of them is a chef so bad that picking him would be downright embarrassing as a human being.
Here is that chef.
You all know who it is already, right?
It’s Master of Gakuzuke Check, cooking amateur, Chef Masatoshi Hamada.
He’s so awkward, isn’t he?
That’s way too much.
You’re just dumping it in at random.
You’re going to kill all the flavor.
That said, he really went all in this time, starting the beef stew five days ago and simmering it for days.
For the doria, he just quickly checked a recipe on YouTube right before recording
and whipped it up on the spot.
Even though Chef Hamada is an amateur,
he does have a record of fooling the taste buds of 36 top celebrities so far.
Of course, if you choose the absolutely-no-good Chef Hamada,
your rank will drop by two levels.
That’s only fair.
Exactly.
All right, everyone, please move to the next area.
This will be a check for all of you.
Work it out together nicely, without fighting, and come to an answer.
First up, the team that was in tears after a solo victory earlier,
and managed to stay at the rank of Ordinary Celebrity.
Team Tendo & Emiko, with over 100 years of showbiz experience between them.
Yes, I’ll definitely be able to tell.
You can tell, right?
Yes, I can.
I’ve hosted a cooking talk show here for 27 years,
and I’ve done about 200 dishes on YouTube as well.
All cooked by myself.
Just leave this to me.
She got the last one right all by herself,
I'm in a great mood now.
This time we have a special rule: beef stew and doria,
and each member in a team will eat a different one.
So, what are you having?
I’ll have the beef stew.
I’ll have the doria.
The Michelin chef’s beef stew
luxuriously uses Tokachi Herb Beef, a premium brand from Hokkaido.
It’s based on a veal stock made from beef bones,
then slowly simmered for three days with meat, aromatic vegetables, red wine, and more,
creating a dish packed with concentrated umami.
The doria uses Daisen chicken from Tottori, known for its rich, flavorful fat.
Rice cooked in chicken broth is topped with a béchamel sauce
that’s packed with concentrated chicken flavor.
The refined taste of the chicken fills your mouth with flavor.
While the ingredients are slightly different,
you can try similar dishes at Lapetit, a bistro in the same restaurant group run by Chef Matsumoto.
It doesn’t feel out of place at all.
Yes it does
First, beef stew A.
How are you going to eat?
Open your mouth.
I’ll open my mouth.
Ueno has hosted a cooking show for 27 years.
She absolutely wants to get this one right.
Meanwhile, Tendo is in charge of the doria.
Can she redeem herself after being the sole loser on the wine check?
Next up is B.
All you have to do is pick the real Michelin chef.
If you pick Hamada’s cooking and drop two ranks,
it’s basically like telling the whole world you’ve got a dumb tongue.
She's really chomping away.
You two are impressive.
And the answer they chose is...
Ready... go!
They matched.
Such tender meat.
The sauce was...
seasoned just right, you know?
It's mellow, with a really rich depth of flavor.
You get that hit of umami, like, 'wow, this is good.'
I'm going with A.
Our choice is A.
Hamada, how many people do you think you can fool?
No idea.
When it comes to this, though, I am pretty confident.
Their answers match: Team Emiko Tendo chooses A.
Yeah, I think we did pretty well with that.
But what happens next is completely unexpected.
Michelin Check: next up, the regular actors.
We should be fine.
As long as we don't pick Hamada's.
We won't pick his.
I actually want you to pick mine, though.
The dish is...
Beef stew.
Doria
What about this one, I wonder.
It doesn't feel out of place at all.
Yeah, totally natural.
Good morning.
These two have a certain air of elegance about them.
Even the way they eat looks refined.
For the sake of the new drama that's about to start,
they can't afford to get knocked out here.
He was nodding.
And kind of laughing, too.
Yeah, he's laughing.
What kind of laugh is that supposed to be?
I mean, I can't tell, it's just too good.
Do they really know what they're doing?
Split
I was torn between C and A
But definitely A
Absolutely A
Totally different
I will bet on your confidence
2 teams going to A
Respecting Daichi's opinion, they head to Room A, where Kaminuma and Tendo are waiting.
Welcome!
Thank goodness.
How was it?
Was the gratin hard to judge?
It was doria.
Doria, doria.
Doria.
That very first bite was insanely good.
It was so good, like something out of a movie.
Team Ordinary Hiromi Go and Team Ordinary Koda Kumi.
You won't pick Hamada's dish, right?
Right.
We are not picking Hamada's.
Yeah, of course not.
Got it.
The two who bragged they could definitely spot Chef Hamada's cooking.
Can they really identify his flavor?
The answers they give are...
Ready...
Whoa, C.
They're split.
They split.
Oh man, what do we do?
Hang on a second.
Here we've got A, B, and C...
For the first time, their answers are split three ways.
So, for everyone watching at home,
we'll now reveal the correct answer you've been waiting for.
The chef with the correct dish is...
This is it...
C.
The one I cooked was...
Now we'll briefly introduce Chef Hamada's recipes for the beef stew
and the doria.
First, the beef stew.
He pours in red wine like there's no tomorrow,
then simmers it down for five days for a seriously committed dish.
The secret ingredient is miso
For a hidden accent, he adds hatcho miso, giving it a smooth, mellow finish.
For the doria, sauté the chicken in butter,
then season it with consommé.
Adjust the white sauce with salt and pepper,
and finally heap on plenty of cheese, and it's done.
I'm kind of happy about that.
Better than ending up in a room with nobody else.
I'd hate that.
It's rough being stuck in here, it really is.
Yeah, I really hated it.
I just wanted someone, anyone, to come.
But even if you're not alone, it's still a wrong answer.
Both pairs drop down to second-rate.
Meanwhile, Koda ended up choosing Hamada's B.
The team's fate now rests with Hiromi Go.
I was torn between A and C.
If that's the case, I see 'A' as Hamachan's.
No way it's C.
I'm telling you, it can't be A.
I'll pick C then?
Or A, right?
No, it's definitely not A.
Amazing.
Seriously amazing.
Then let's go with C.
Should we pick C?
You really shouldn't rely on me
No, at this point...
I think we should bet on Hiromi.
Koda-san, are you...
Are you really talking casually to Hiromi Go?
That just isn't right.
Thanks to Go...
Hot, hot, that's hot!
(Go's Livin la Vida Loca cover)
They dodged Hamada and nailed the right answer!
Go! Go! Go!
An empty room...
No, B's flavor was a bit too strong.
Ah! Two votes for A.
Huh? No way! I said A was Hama-chan's.
Even if you say that, we still can't tell.
Seriously? 'A' is Hama-chan's, you know.
Yeah, that side dish felt kind of like a punk's cooking.
He's pretty cool!
They keep saying 'A' is Hama-chan's.
But that can't be right, can it?
No way, definitely not.
A is the pro's dish.
'A' is from Ox, the long-established Western-style restaurant run by the Sato brothers.
Their beef stew is based on a special sauce that has been built up for over 50 years.
They add tomato purée, wine, vegetables, and beef,
then simmer it for over three hours to create a rich, concentrated flavor.
As for the doria, they mix in supermarket-bought chicken and cook it together with the rice,
top it with a cheesy, creamy béchamel sauce, and bake it to finish.
If they pick Hamada here, they'll drop down to the 'look-alike' rank.
Team '50-Minute Lover'.
Mio-san makes desserts...
at a professional level,
he brought individually wrapped madeleines to the set, they looked like they were from a store
He makes them himself?
Yes, he actually bakes them.
So when it comes to food,
I won't
make a mistake.
Takahashi is absolutely confident in his cooking skills.
He wants to nail the real Michelin dish,
and somehow hang on to that second-rate rank.
The answer they gave is...
Ready, set...
ahh... total split!
Wow totally split
Split!
These 3...
Which answer will they pick?
Mitsuomi good job!
He has the confidence about food but...
dumb tongue
A is definitely wrong
I was thinking B is definitely not it.
Tae, you went with A, right?
I figured it had to be either A or C.
We're all kind of ignoring B, aren't we?
Mitsuomi say something, will you?
Then if it's between those, I guess C.
Why won't you go for B, huh?
All right, then...
We'll go with C, please.
Either way, they got it right. Nicely done.
They were split between A, B, and C and it was a gamble,
but they managed to converge on the correct answer and just barely stay in the second tier.
The votes are split.
No one picked B.
I actually chose B.
Right, Mitsuomi-san, you went with B.
The B doria was really tasty, though.
It was the best one.
Our second-rate idols, Fruits-something-or-other.
All right, Fruits...
Zipper, yeah.
Fruits Zipper, how are you feeling?
When there's something to celebrate, our boss takes us to this super fancy place in Roppongi...
Don't say that.
You can't be going around saying stuff like that.
So far, the ones who picked Chef Hamada are...
only Koda Kumi and Mitsuomi Takahashi
But still, no team has picked the 'absolutely no good' dish.
Can they avoid it here as well
and earn a reward from their boss,
getting taken to a nice restaurant in Roppongi?
Now, their answer is...
Ready, and...
Four out of five chose B.
So it's B... that's Hamada's dish right?
That's really good.
No way, does that actually happen?
I felt like the natural sweetness and the tenderness of the meat were really high quality.
These kids are so sweet.
I thought B was the most properly made as a dish.
Okay, then let's go with B.
All right, we'll choose B.
Okay.
All right.
Here it comes.
Now you can open your first restaurant
But A and C didn't seem all that shocked.
Yeah, exactly.
More like, 'Oh, is that so.'
'Ahh, yeah, we picked that one...' kind of reaction.
The group formerly known as Fruits Zipper, now Fruits Chuck
has chosen Chef Hamada and fallen to the look-alike tier.
Wait, hold on, that's bad!
What do we do?
You’ve got to be kidding.
This is scary, seriously.
Wait!
Hey!
This could be Hamada's food
True.
Can Team Yoshimoto hang on to their normal-celebrity status?
If we survive this round, it’s huge.
It really tests our teamwork too.
I pretty much cook for myself every day.
I cook a ton.
Have you ever eaten Hamada’s cooking?
Yeah!
I had it when we did a show together.
You can tell right away when a dish is missing love, you know?
So if you feel like there’s no love in it, that one’s Hamada’s
On the menu: the Batteries duo get doria, and Atsushi gets beef stew.
Earlier, at the 8 strings round, Atsushi’s mistake knocked them out of top-rank status.
As the senior, he can’t drag his juniors down any further.
We’re supposed to guess which one is Hamada’s, right?
No! You’re unbelievably dumb.
What the hell are you talking about?
So, what’s your answer?
Ready, set...
Huh?
Whoa.
This time Atsushi got it right.
No, but this is…
Everyone ends up going back and forth between A and C.
It’s not B.
Lively bunch.
I think A is Hamada.
It’s A isn’t it, Hamada?
Hmm, that’s what it feels like.
For me it’s overwhelmingly A, though.
The beef stew?
The meat quality in B, and how smooth the stew is...
B… B is Hamada’s.
Yeah, B. B has to be Hamada’s.
B tasted like something I’ve had before.
So between A and C, if I go with A and I’m wrong, it’s like, man, I’m really off my game.
At least for today.
Just for today.
Batteries keep getting them right, so I’m gonna ride with them.
I see.
Alright then, I’ll change my answer.
Is it okay if we all line up together on this one?
Yeah.
Today you kinda want to stick with Batteries, right?
Yeah, it ends up like that.
Classic rating check move: one wrong answer and everyone loses their nerve.
They followed the hot-handed Batteries... and sadly, they were wrong.
Hey, welcome.
Alright, alright.
This is a nice turn of events.
I'm so relieved!
Chef Hamada’s dishes have fooled the palates of countless celebrities.
Can they keep dodging his cooking from here on out?
All they have to do is pick the dish made by a Michelin-starred chef.
Kis-My-Ft2, the totally normal idol group now in their 15th year.
Last time, the fried rice Hamada made...
That was insanely good, right?
It was crazy good.
Yeah, it was really good.
See? See?
Pick me
This year, all the members are taking part.
It’s an omen for how 2026 will go, too.
They can’t possibly pick Chef Hamada’s dish on New Year’s Day...
...and drop two whole ranks right off the bat.
Can they avoid Chef Hamada’s dish?
Ready, go!
That’s impressive.
Everyone picked C.
Awesome.
Everyone?
That’s wild.
C it is.
All C.
C?
Kis-My-Ft2 is gonna last another 50 years at this rate.
Didn’t think they’d be this in sync.
They’ve been together since they were kids.
That’s true.
All six of these close-knit members chose the same one and nailed it.
They keep their normal-celebrity ranking.
Oh!
Thank goodness.
If we clear this, I feel like
everyone will finally acknowledge us.
Yeah, let’s get that recognition.
(not recognized)
Last up is Lord GACKT, currently on an 84-win streak.
The dish is beef stew.
Lord GACKT once got it right after tasting just two grains of rice.
He checks the flavor with that incredibly sensitive tongue of his.
It’s hard to imagine he’d ever pick Chef Hamada’s dish...
But GACKT actually knows that Hamada’s safe, basic flavors can taste good.
Will he be able to choose C, the correct answer?
Hmm...
He's rarely hesitant
What made you settle on that answer?
How well the sauce soaked in.
And the smoothness of the sauce.
And how deep the flavor is.
Compared to the others,
this one is on a whole different level.
Fundamentally, the sauce just has way more depth of flavor.
So I think you can really tell the difference.
So, has Lord GACKT actually chosen the correct answer, C?
Time to reveal the life-changing result!
All right, here we go.
Please...
Please...Hamada-san!
Hamada-san!
I'm begging you...
We'll open the door of my food first.
Then I really don't want anyone coming in here
(uselessly holding hands)
It's the 'down two ranks' room...
No, don't do this.
Please stop.
Don't come in, don't come in, don't come in, don't come in!
Stop...
No way!
I knew it!
Nice!
Knew it.
Just as I thought.
Yeah, this feels right.
You girls are amazing, seriously.
You have the most delicious food!
Thank you for the meal.
So good, so good, so good, so good.
You're gonna be famous for a long time.
Now, we'll open the door with the correct answer.
No, I hate this...
I really hate this...
(useless praying)
The correct answer is...
Please come
(Not coming)
Is this...
Hiromi good job!
(really depressed)
I'm really sorry!
Will Lord GACKT extend his 84 wins by picking C?
What is the fate of GACKT?
All right then,
Well, obviously he'll be in here.
I knew it.
Knew it.
Those young girls.
They really are young.
as expected...
Those Fruits Zipper kids really have
no taste buds
Yay! How long is this streak gonna go on?
Lord Gackt's winning streak is now updated to 85.
With two questions left, the look-alikes are already on the brink.
If no-taste Fruits Chuck get the next one wrong, they'll disappear.
For fakes like them, this kind of treatment is more than generous
All right, our incorrect players have returned.
Come on in.
Huh? What is she holding?
For those who got it wrong,
we have a little souvenir: Yoshimoto Curry.
We'll be handing it out to you.
Lucky...
It's the number one favorite at the company cafeteria.
Here you go, please take it home with you.
You can get this if you go to the theater, you know.
I've eaten so much of this!
Our apologies, everyone.
We thought all of you were actual celebrities,
but it turns out one group was just look-alikes. Sorry about that.
People always say you look just like them, right?
We're Fruits...
Chuck.
We're Fruits Chuck.
You gave up your own name
From today, you're Fruits Chuck.
We have a quick announcement for everyone here.
The Fruits Zipper members
called Chef Hamada's beef stew delicious,
and we've recreated that very beef stew:
Hamada Beef Stew will now be available for purchase.
Yes,
that's right.
Using Chef Hamada's recipe,
Hamada Beef Stew
will be sold at 7-Eleven stores nationwide,
for a limited time from noon tomorrow, January 2nd,
rolling out store by store.
And that's not all.
Chef Hamada also created dishes for last year's spring and fall editions of this show,
using recipes that fooled five top-class celebrities, and we've recreated those as well.
First, Hamada Omurice.
And with its fragrant ginger
and soy sauce aroma as the key flavors, Hamada Fried Chicken
is already being sold as a fried chicken bento at 7-Eleven stores nationwide,
for a limited time.
After you finish watching the show,
Pick one up at your nearest 7-Eleven.
We appreciate your support.
Thank you very much.