***Subtitles Ardarvin & Mayumi***
'Celebrity Ranking Check 2026: New Year Special'
It begins! 2026 Celebrity Ranking Check Special!
Start your year with your first big laugh on this show.
Kick off a wonderful year in the best mood possible.
Do you think this is going to be pretty difficult?
The six checks that top-class celebrities should normally ace
are extra tough this year, with one surprise after another.
A famous actor has a sword fight
A legend sings a classic hit,
and the nonstop shocking checks have emotions exploding everywhere
tears for some,
'We did it!' for others!
Mega-level bombshell moments just keep coming.
There is literally nothing but highlights.
GACKT-sama is on an 81-win streak
Who dares to face him this year?
All right, here we go!
'Celebrity Ranking Check 2026.'
Competing are top-tier celebrities from all walks of entertainment.
Let us introduce the eight teams.
First up,
A man who has always stayed at the forefront of the industry,
Go Hiromi-sama, who will celebrate the 55th anniversary of his debut next year,
And the artist who blew up with her 'sexy and cool' songs and performances,
Kumi Koda-sama, marking the 25th anniversary of her debut this year.
It's an anniversary year for them both.
Team Anniversary: Hiromi Go & Kumi Koda!
Let's have fun with it.
But, Hiromi-san, you know,
it's fine.
I mean, as a sort of celebration,
I heard it's 70, right?
You still look so youthful.
So I really want us to win as a birthday gift.
We've prepared a practice question to predict how they'll do today.
The warm-up challenge for Team Anniversary is popcorn.
All you have to do is pick the expensive one, A.
My face must look ridiculous right now.
I've got no clue with something like this.
I'll start with A.
These two are entering a very special anniversary year.
They really can't afford to miss such an easy pre-game question.
Their answers are...
One, two...
Okay!
Split!
Then let's go with the one on the right.
Yeah.
Wrong!
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
Just do whatever you want.
Kumi-chan, never ever lose that innocent, free-spirited side of you.
Be bold and own it.
Got it.
Uh, Hiromi...
Calling Hiromi-sama just 'Hiromi' is a bold innocence
But if a musician messes this one up,
they should probably just retire, right?
Retire!
Don't say that!
Will the wrong answer mean an early New Year retirement?
Yesterday's Red and White Song Battle was a huge success,
and Fruits Zipper are exploding in popularity as a national idol group.
Five members from the group are joining us today.
Who do you think will be the key member?
When it comes to food,
Chinsei-san's the one.
I love food.
The check for Fruits Zipper is seaweed.
By the way, for all the warm-up questions, the correct answer is always A.
And the answer is...
Everyone got it right!
Yay!
We got this!
Pretty good start, right?
This is awesome!
We can totally do this!
We're first-class!
Whenever something good happens, our president always ________
Don't say that!
Fruits Zipper are out to leave a serious impression on this year's Ranking Check.
These girls are really sweet.
Go on, Fruits Chuck!
Zipper!
Next up,
A slightly out-of-sync couple's offbeat, heart-throbbing love story.
From the drama '50-Minute Lover,' premiering Sunday, January 18,
Kei Inoo-sama from Hey! Say! JUMP,
Kimura Tae-sama
Takahashi Mitsuomi-sama.
Their warm-up question is...
miso.
The answers they gave are...
A clearly has a bit more
depth to it
For me, it tasted a bit salty.
Yeah, I found it salty too.
Um, I'll go with B.
OK, then let's say B.
With the drama leads putting their heads together...
Buzzer!
See? That wasn't so bad, was it?
You're right.
In the main game, there will definitely be food questions too.
Mitsuomi is an amazing cook, that's really his specialty.
So when it comes to taste, he's going to be seriously strong.
Just, when it comes to miso...
I am not making miso-flavored madeleines.
Let me make that clear right now.
Takahashi Mitsuomi, who's has already made a mistake, is actually a key player on this team?
Will he be okay?
Thanks for telling me nothing useful.
Next up,
Team Yoshimoto: Atsushi Tamura and the two members of Batteries, who blew up in popularity last year.
The warm-up question: a premium butter you spread on bread crusts and eat.
The wrong answer is something totally different: margarine.
Their answer is...
Whaaat?
'B'?
As in 'B' for 'butter'?
No! How stupid do you think we are?
On this one, you should go with me.
You sure about that?
For real, I use really good butter at home.
At home? You should have led with that.
Since I use good butter at home, it's this one.
And... wrong.
Totally useless! Go throw that 'good butter' away.
So this is just hopeless now, huh?
Is it really hopeless?
But when it counts, I'm crazy strong, so if it's the real thing...
No, trust me in the real thing.
Seriously, I pull off stuff even I can't believe.
You sure about that?
I really do better in the actual show.
The entertainment world's most fastidious man.
Batteries decide to trust their veteran senior, Atsushi Tamura, and follow his lead.
But a shocking falling-out leaves them in a state beyond repair.
This is a total disaster.
And what everyone is most curious about is...
Nobody misses a question this easy.
I honestly don't get how you get this wrong.
GACKT-sama, currently on a record-breaking personal streak of 81 straight wins.
Who on earth will be his partner this time?
One day in October, a message arrived from GACKT-sama to the show producer.
'It's been a while. This is GACKT.'
'I have something to discuss regarding this year's Ranking Check appearance.'
'Could you come to Malaysia next Wednesday?'
That's right, GACKT-sama lives in Malaysia.
He summoned us to Malaysia as casually as if it were a meeting in downtown Tokyo.
But this had to be something important.
'Understood.'
'I'll come.'
What could this be about?
About seven hours by plane from Japan.
After arriving in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, we
headed straight to GACKT-sama's mansion.
Beyond these tight security gates
lies GACKT-sama's residence.
Over nine hours after leaving Japan,
we can finally hear what GACKT-sama has to say.
This fortress-like estate is GACKT-sama's home.
Just getting to the front door is already a struggle.
And finally...
We were greeted by GACKT-sama's local staff.
Um, is GACKT-sama here?
GACKT is currently out on business.
Yes, could you wait inside for a while?
Oh, I see, that's the situation.
Wait, we came all the way from Japan like he asked, and GACKT-sama isn't even here?
I'm sorry.
Alright then, we'll wait inside.
This place really is incredible.
Where is GACKT-sama, and what is he doing?
Can you please wait for a second? I will contact GACKT-sama
While they got in touch with GACKT-sama, we secretly took a look around the mansion.
The first thing that caught our eye was his trademark collection of sunglasses.
Then a bunch of accessories that just scream 'expensive.'
And in his custom gym, where he trains every day,
Here is GACKT-sama's original workout list.
You know what, let's sneak a look at the garage too.
Inside were an Evangelion-themed Lamborghini and a Jaguar.
Their emblems were sparkling bright.
After waiting for an hour,
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Yes, thank you for waiting.
Apparently GACKT is tied up and can't get away right now.
Tied up?
He asked to please come where he is instead.
Got it. Could you take us to where he is?
Yes, of course.
We appreciate it.
If he's that tied up, what exactly is he doing there?
He's doing something a bit dangerous.
I see...
Something dangerous? Where on earth are they taking us?
The thing he wants to discuss better not be not appearing on the show at all
Entertainer Ranking Check 2026.
The total value of the instruments used by the 8 piece orchestra will break the show's all-time record.
An astonishing 10.24 billion yen.
The standout among them is this violin.
The Stradivarius 'Corbett.'
This 'Corbett' has an exceptionally limited repair history.
The condition of this original wood from 300 years ago
has been preserved in the best possible state.
This will be shown in Japan for the very first time
exclusively on this ranking check show.
After three years of negotiations,
it is finally making its Japan debut.
It is the most expensive item in the show's history,
worth 2.5 billion yen.
Here is how it sounds.
There's no escape now.
Damn, they totally outmaneuvered us.
This time, eight teams are taking part.
Next up,
Top idols who headline concerts at all five major domes,
Kis-My-Ft2, celebrating their 15th anniversary.
This time, the entire group is here together.
The warm-up question for Kis-My-Ft2 is
tsurume (dried squid).
And the answer they chose is...
We're split.
We're pretty much divided half and half.
It's our first time on this show.
Yeah, it really is Takashi's first time.
You can be the one to decide.
B!
Boo!
What a terrible start.
Takashi...
When I watched this show on TV it looked so fun.
I get a lot of them right when watching.
Seriously?
That's what everyone watching at home says.
All six members of Kis-My-Ft2 join forces as one,
and pull off a miracle never before seen on this show.
No way!
That's amazing.
Next,
'Okome no Onna', a drama set in the National Tax Agency, starting Thursday, January 8,
and the human love mystery 'Saikai', starting Tuesday, January 13.
First, Daichi Mao and Takeuchi Ryoma.
Their warm-up question is about umeboshi (pickled plums).
And the answer they gave is...
This one was more sour, but in a refined way,
so I figured it had to be the more expensive one.
Then A.
I'm sorry if I'm wrong.
Brilliant   that's correct.
Thank goodness.
I want to stay top tier.
I want to go home with a pleasant feeling.
Ryoma Takeuchi,
you're way too fired up for New Year's?!
I went with the taste, I guess.
I focused on the flavor.
Didn't you just get drunk on the red wine?
And lastly, from the world of entertainment,
our superstar veteran team.
B.
(eliminated. not worth showing)
We have Emiko Kaminuma, who was eliminated last time,
and YOSHIMI TENDO making her first appearance.
I left home today really pumped up for this.
I'm not kidding, for the past three days
I've been telling myself I'm going to be the last one standing.
I came here thinking my rival is GACKT.
And I, too,
as a first-rate entertainer,
am here today with a lot of pride.
We're going to get every single question right.
We've each been in show business for 50 years
that's 100 years between us.
Their warm-up question is beef heart.
Hatsu is super common at yakiniku places in Kansai.
And the answer they gave is...
Are they the same?
The depth of the flavor is different.
Ah, they're different.
Okay.
We're done for.
From here?
From here
Tendo-saaan!
It's okay.
This legendary duo with over 100 years of showbiz experience between them
runs wild all over the place!
Why are you acting like the host?
We're going to do something a bit dangerous now.
GACKT suddenly summons them to Malaysia for a meeting.
They drive off with his staff
Without being told where they're going.
After 1 hour they're surrounded by untouched nature.
After 2 hours they are deep into the mountains.
What dangerous thing is GACKT doing out in a jungle like this?
What on earth is he up to? He's not doing anything shady... right?
After three hours in the car...
'This way, please.'
Here?
Yes.
They're taken to a place where lots of dogs are wandering around,
a place that is clearly not normal by any stretch.
Isn't this kind of sketchy?
It is sketchy.
Yeah, it definitely feels that way.
Please get on this boat.
Huh? We're getting on a boat?
Where's GACKT?
Once we get there, I think you'll be able to meet GACKT.
Is this boat actually safe?
It's fine.
What's your name?
Lei
Take care. I hope you get to him safely.
This is where we say goodbye to GACKT's staff.
From here, we head to GACKT on Mr. Lei's sketchy-looking boat.
Fourteen hours from Japan, switching between plane, car, and boat.
Where on earth is GACKT and what is he doing?
Ignoring our worries, Mr. Lei's boat heads deep into the jungle.
There are wild animals along the shore.
(cow)
(monkey)
(buffalo)
According to Mr. Lei, even tigers and leopards live here. It's a place that basically shuts people out.
Whoa, that beehive is huge.
Mr. Lei says one sting from those and you're dead.
Is GACKT really in a place this dangerous?
We ride the boat for another hour.
Pushing through the bushes, we come to...
Huh? There’s someone there.
That kinda looks like GACKT.
Nervously, we call out to him.
Excuse me, are you GACKT?
Good morning.
I can't see his face, but he really seems like GACKT.
That must've taken you a long time, right?
It took us almost 14 hours.
Can we talk on the boat?
Over here. Yes.
This cool-looking boat?
Is this yours, GACKT?
Yeah, it's mine.
Sorry if this sounds rude, but...
You really are GACKT, right?
Long time no see.
Ouch!
This firm handshake has got to be GACKT.
Could you maybe just show us your face, just to be sure?
I get sunburned, you know.
See?
Ah, it really is GACKT.
I told you, that hurts.
By the way, GACKT, what are you doing all the way out here?
I was out fishing, but my car broke down and I couldn’t get back.
So that’s why we couldn’t meet you at your place.
That's right, I'm sorry.
They just put us on a boat without telling us anything, and it took over an hour to get here.
Nobody knows about this spot, not even the locals.
So it's nice, no one bothers me out here.
What were you fishing for here?
A fish called toman.
Toman?
Yeah, it's a fish called the giant snakehead.
Toman are snakehead fish that live widely across Southeast Asia.
They're smarter than largemouth bass and much harder to catch.
Is this lure fishing?
Yeah, it is.
When did you start?
I got hooked on it about three years ago.
And I've been coming out here ever since.
You need this many rods just to fish for toman?
This is all tackle.
They're all different types of rods.
When we saw your house earlier, there was a crazy amount of fishing gear.
That’s not a shop, right?
No, it’s not.
I kept testing different things and it just piled up.
You’re an artist, so why are you so obsessed with fishing?
Right now, Japan’s fishing industry is in a slump.
But Japanese tackle makers are still among the best in the world.
So seeing the Japanese market shrink this much feels kind of sad, you know?
So I started wondering if there was something I could do to support it.
But if you’re not actually good at it, no one will take you seriously.
That’s why I practice.
Apparently, he’s working on some kind of fishing entertainment project.
Here’s GACKT reeling in a toman.
Once he gets into something, GACKT takes it to the extreme.
Now, they say he’s one of the top anglers in Malaysia when it comes to toman.
Toman can grow to about 13 kilos and are dangerous enough to bite off a human finger.
Another thing that caught our eye was his bookshelf at home.
It was lined with language books. How many languages can you speak now, GACKT?
In Malaysia, English is the main language I use.
I’ve got a lot of Chinese friends too, so I speak Mandarin as well.
And when I meet my Korean friends, I speak a bit of Korean.
I also saw some French books.
I haven’t used French at all lately.
I’ve gotten rusty… or more like I’ve forgotten most of it.
There were quite a few books about conversations between men and women, though.
What are you looking at those for?
Is that the easiest way to remember things?
Well, you’re most motivated when it comes to flirting, right?
So, what kind of year was 2025 for you?
Let me think…
it was a year of preparing to fully restart my music activities in 2026.
I was doing films and dramas and such.
But mostly, I spent the year laying the groundwork for music.
From 2026, I’m really getting back into it.
So you already have concrete plans for your activities?
I’ll do a world tour, then head to South America.
And from March, I’ll start a project called 'LAST SONGS' with K.
Wow, that’s insanely busy.
I’m really diving back into music again.
My health is finally back to normal.
I’m really looking forward to that, seriously.
You suddenly emailed saying you needed to talk, but what exactly about the Rating Check did you want to discuss?
That's right.
Last year was pretty rough, wasn't it?
Yeah, on last year's Rating Check...
Stupid tongue!
On the final question, because of my partner's huge blunder, we were eliminated.
I knew it was going to end up like that.
GACKT's prediction was spot-on.
Even GACKT disappeared from the screen.
So when you say you wanted to talk, is this about your partner?
In 2026 I'll finally be restarting my music career,
Who did GACKT pick for his partner?
So who on earth is it?
Who is GACKT's partner this time?
In 2026 I'll finally be restarting my music career,
and I kind of felt I didn't want anyone getting in my way.
I want to finish with a completely perfect score
and start off 2026 in the best possible way.
So this time, I was thinking I would go in alone.
I was thinking of doing it by myself, and whether that was okay or not,
I wanted to get your judgment on that.
Last year really
stuck with me for months.
I see, so it was like that for you.
But taking it on alone is a pretty harsh choice, isn't it?
Of course I know it's going to be hard,
but the hardest thing of all is relationships, right?
Right now,
when it comes to them,
I've kind of lost trust.
The thing is, we've already made offers to those two.
Then let's have them on in 2027
Understood.
If you're willing to go that far, GACKT,
then this time, let's have you go in alone.
All right, thank you very much.
Hey, I told you, that hurts!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.