***Subtitles generated by Whisper V3 translated by GPT5.3 edited by Ardarvin & Mayumi***
Celebrity Ranking Check 2026
New Year's Special
All right, let's kick off this year with a big burst of energy!
Celebrity Ranking Check 2026
New Year's Special
To all our top-tier celebrities,
Happy New Year!
As expected of you all.
You're looking sharp.
Well, you're first-class celebrities, as always.
Eight teams will be taking the test.
First up is Team 81 Wins in a Row: GACKT-sama
Since you're on your own today, that means you're carrying everything by yourself.
2026 is a big year for me, I've got a world tour and everything,
so it's important.
You'd like to get a good start to the year?
I have to stay as first-class: finally this show has figured out how I should be treated.
Well, you are all by yourself, and with a record like that...
...we've really thought it through.
Sorry, I've been bothered by something I noticed...
That is something else.
This was custom-made.
You had it made?
Yeah, a special order.
It's all diamonds.
I had it made fully in diamonds.
And today, we'll give this away to a viewer!
Why would you do that?
Why on earth?
I only put it on for the first time today!
Sorry, but...
How much?
This is about 3,000.
Huh? 3,000 yen?
No, no,
3,000 man (1 man = 10,000 yen)
Yeah, seriously.
Next, from Team Kansai's Two Great Stars, representing Kansai entertainment...
Yoshimi Tendo and Emiko Kaminuma.
It's my first time on this show,
but I really want to get every single question right.
That's my goal. For today.
That's what everyone's aiming for.
Exactly.
Yes.
But if you get one wrong, Tendo, it means Kaminuma will drop down a rank with you.
That's right.
So I'm really counting on you.
You're just piling on the pressure!
But how about you, Kaminuma?
Last time, I disappeared from the screen.
That's right.
My reputation took a hit.
People were saying, So much for the so-called Empress of Kansai, she's not that great after all.'
So today is my revenge.
Today, yes.
From Team Anniversary, celebrating his 55th debut anniversary next year, Hiromi Go,
and celebrating her 25th anniversary this year, Kumi Koda.
Hiromi, how are you feeling?
I think we'll be fine.
By the way, on the 2022 New Year's special, Hiromi Go actually got down on his knees and bowed in apology,
because his final ranking was third-rate celebrity.
He literally did a full-on dogeza apology.
You think he'll do that again?
I'm determined not to let him kneel like that ever again.
Yes, exactly.
I'm going to give it everything today.
From the much-talked-about new drama The Rice Woman and Our Reunion,'
we have Mao Daichi and Ryoma Takeuchi.
Daichi-sama how do you feel?
I'll do my best.
In 2019, you were paired with Hiromi Go,
and you finished as first-class celebrities.
You think you'll do it again?
Well, of course.
But back then, I really relied on Hiromi-san a lot.
He practically carried me the whole way.
Oh, is that so?
Then you're obviously doomed this time.
No, no, no!
Takeuchi...
In a previous special side edition of Ranking Check,
you were rated as a second-rate celebrity.
That was just the side-show, though.
In the main show, you're strong.
Well, you see,
I've gotten through a lot of growing pains,
I've grown up properly,
and I've learned to appreciate the finer things in life.
From the new drama 50-Minute Lover,' we have Hey! Say! JUMP's
Kei Inoo, Tae Kimura, and Mitsuomi Takahashi.
I can confidently say we've got this.
The reputation of our drama is on the line.
When your opinions split, which way you decide to lean is going to be crucial.
But he's the lead of the drama, you know.
He's really good at making decisions.
So with a little help from these two,
let's all go down together, shall we?
Mitsuomi-san, how about you?
Well, this time we absolutely cannot let Kimura-san
get knocked out of this top seat.
So we're going to dig in, make sure we don't mess up,
and we will not get a single one wrong.
Saying something totally normal in a way that makes it sound complicated.
This year the whole group is here together.
Everyone from Team Kis-My-Ft2.
Everyone except Nikaido joined us for last New Year 2025 and ended up classed as second-rate, right?
They were second-rate?
But this time, for the first time,
with everyone here.
Now that the whole team is together, we are going to make it to first-rate.
No, no, no.
I really watched last year's broadcast,
yeah, I watched it.
And I kept going, like, 'No, that's wrong, it's not that one.'
I was yelling, 'That one, pick that one!'
You got every single one right?
If you just think simply, you can definitely tell.
So we were just overthinking it.
That's true.
Right.
From Team Yoshimoto,
we have this fun trio.
Mr. Atsushi Tamura,
and Batteries-sama.
You finally invited us, huh.
What are you even talking about?
I'm actually really confident about this.
I've eaten all kinds of great food,
all sorts of high-quality stuff.
If nothing else, I know how to spot the good things.
How about your answers, how confident are you?
Me, I was literally the official taste-tester in my family.
My mom would say,
'Hey, try this for me,' and hand it over,
and my role was to say, 'It's all delicious,' no matter what.
Yeah.
That's a pretty fun job.
So he's a man who really knows his mom's cooking.
Super popular idols make their first appearance on the Ranking Check.
From Team FRUITS ZIPPER, we have these five members.
We are FRUITS ZIPPER.
Thank you for having us.
You're really going for a synchronized look?
It's a necessary greeting, yes.
How do you feel? We'll be doing all kinds of checks today.
We always check out good food.
Oh really?
And also drinks, alcohol too.
I'll take charge of that part.
There'll be music and various other things this time as well.
We're confident when it comes to music.
Dance is Alafy's area,
and Mizuiro's too.
(good luck)
Everyone, please take a look over here.
Here, you see these portraits
These go up on the wall if you achieve first-rate twice.
You can see the numbers there.
Mr. GACKT has already made first-rate ten times.
Who is close from today's participants?
Hiromi Go, Daiichi Maou, and Koda Kumi are all one step away.
If those three stay first-rate again today, that'll make it twice for them,
and they'll be up on that wall.
Exactly.
Well, you know...
Hiromi-san is really sharp with this stuff.
But I keep thinking he's going to slip up somewhere.
These 24 participants
will be putting their status as top-tier celebrities on the line
and taking on the checks.
The first check
is this one.
Of course, it's wine.
As always, we've prepared luxury wines
costing no less than one million yen a bottle.
We have the finest wines ready for you.
From Bordeaux in France,
the five great châteaux would be far too obvious for our first-rate guests,
so this time, we've picked something that even Mr. GACKT has probably never tasted before,
a very special wine.
Now, let us introduce it.
It is Château La Mission Haut-Brion.
Check 1: Wine.
From Bordeaux, France: Château La Mission Haut-Brion.
One bottle: 1,000,000 yen.
La Mission stands across the road from its twin Château Haut-Brion, one of the five great châteaux
The vintage is 1947, about 80 years ago.
In Japan, that was two years after the end of the war, the year the Japanese Constitution was enacted.
The wine was selected by the Ranking Check's resident sommelier, Chika Noguchi.
From fermentation, vinification, and aging,
it develops a rich aroma and sweetness,
along with a mellow, well-balanced, and profoundly deep flavor.
And what you'll be comparing it to
is a 5,000-yen bottle of wine.
That's right.
So we're talking one million versus five thousand yen.
We almost feel sorry for our first-rate guests,
because this one is practically too easy.
Uh-oh, I see some shifty eyes already.
These are the representatives.
You'd think this one would be a no-brainer, but...
...things take a wildly unexpected turn!
All right, representatives, please come forward.
to the standby room, please.
This is the very first round, so it really matters.
You’ve got to hold your ground here.
We welcome our top-tier celebrities with traditional New Year food and sake.
First up, this guest.
Here he comes.
It is the one and only Mr. GO.
Hiromi Go.
With his outstanding vocals and razor-sharp performances,
he’s been loved across generations for over 50 years.
A true VIP-class superstar.
Thing is, I don’t drink alcohol anymore.
Huh?
You quit around 60 or so, right?
Actually, I stopped even before I hit 60.
So I haven’t had a drink in over ten years.
Are you going to be okay with this?
Big juice.
Yes.
Did you say Big Juice?
I’m fine if we say it’s just big juice.
You sure you’re okay, sir?
Big juice, big juice.
Let’s just pretend it’s basically big juice.
Big-juice Hiromi "Japan" GO!
Let’s start with wine A.
But you really haven’t drunk in over ten years, right?
Alcohol, I mean.
He carefully checks the aroma,
then suddenly takes a quick sip.
He slowly rolls it over his tongue,
and nods.
That was fast, he went right in.
He’s quick, isn’t he?
Alcohol touching his lips for the first time in 10 years
Has he forgotten how to drink?
He cradles the glass with both hands, as if it were a cup of green tea.
Let him just have some tea...
How is it?
So, which one will he choose?
Oh, it’s only one sip each.
You can tell, right? They’re definitely different.
Big-juice Hiromi GO’s answer is...
That was quick.
He decided fast.
I felt like maybe it had aged too long and gotten a bit vinegary.
That’s the impression I got.
And comparing the colors, it seemed to show its age too.
So I thought, yeah, it was leaning a bit toward vinegar.
You keep calling it vinegar...
Hiromi GO! After just one sip of each, he chooses A.
Let’s wait.
Now he waits for the results, watching the others on the monitor.
But Tendo-san has tons of them at home, right? Her cellar’s packed with wine.
Ouch, going up against Professor Tendo...
Next up, this guest.
Here we have Ms. Tendo.
Yoshimi Tendo.
With a one-of-a-kind voice that combines power and delicacy,
she’s a top star who continues to lead the enka world.
Do you drink wine often?
We’ll get together and have some now and then,
but I don’t really down it in big gulps.
I just sip a little at a time.
That’s how you’re supposed to do it.
You’re meant to savor it, hold it in your mouth.
People who chug it are dangerous.
Tendo, who has a huge wine cellar at home, starts with wine A.
She checks the color,
gently lets a sip flow into her mouth,
and slowly rolls it around on her tongue.
She nods, looking confident.
Oh...she looks confident.
Tendo even seems relaxed, totally at ease.
With a sharp gaze, she checks the color,
then gently lets this one flow into her mouth as well.
She's smiles with satisfaction
She knows
Her answer is...
Split answer!
When I first sip...
There’s this soft, really lovely aroma that spreads out.
I’m confident about this.
That’s the opinion of someone who actually drinks.
Right off the bat, they’re split.
The utterly confident Yoshimi Tendo
heads to room B, opposite from GO.
What should I do?
Why is Hiromi-san sitting there all hunched up and tiny like that?
He picked the most awkward spot to sit.
Bad perspective?
Next up is...
Ryoma Takeuchi
a top actor in constant demand for dramas and films, known for his strong presence and wide range of roles.
So, how about wine? Do you usually drink it?
I drink a little wine, yes.
But something in the one-million-yen range, I’ve never...
Right, yeah, of course, of course.
There should be an overwhelming difference between them.
Of course.
I've got all my senses on high alert,
so I feel like I can pull this off.
Will those hypersensitive antennas pick up the right answer?
First up is wine A, chosen by Go.
He's used to this.
It really suits him.
Yeah, he's clearly done this a lot.
He must have practiced somewhere.
He takes two sips of the wine he's been served.
He swirls it, then goes in for the aroma.
Oh, he's gone for a third sip.
Huh?
Takeuchi just keeps drinking.
Go on, just finish the whole thing.
He actually drank it all.
Is he gonna be okay after this?
Next is wine B, chosen by Tendo.
First, he checks the smell.
Hmm?
Did those sharp senses pick up something?
He quickly checks the taste as well.
He's a real drinker.
Okay, here we go.
Just a small sip of this one.
And the answer he gives is...
Oh!
It felt like it had softened over, say, eighty years or so,
like it had really aged and matured.
There was this slight fallen-leaves kind of nuance too.
Listen to this guy.
He's just as confident.
So which one of them is actually right?
Next up...
Atsushi Tamura.
Not only does he host variety shows,
he also appears on news and educational programs,
a top-tier entertainer with a truly broad range.
I really, really wanted to do the wine segment.
Seriously?
I'm a wine lover, I actually go to places like Napa Valley,
and do all kinds of tours
Annoying, right?
I can't help it, I just really love wine.
Very reassuring.
He loves wine so much he even visits the world's most famous wine regions.
With practiced hands, he checks the bouquet.
then smoothly lets it roll over his tongue.
He looks experienced
Next, wine B, which only Tendo chose.
He carefully checks the color first.
He's really studying the color.
Even though those glasses are tinted...
Then take the glasses off!
What's the point otherwise?
True.
You can't see anything with those still on.
With just a single sip of this one,
he goes, 'Wow, that's good.'
Same as before.
Can he really tell?
And his answer is...?
I'm relieved
Knew it.
I was sure it'd be that.
(Could be bad)
When you let it sit in your mouth,
there's this kind of weight to it,
and even an aroma that feels like it carries history.
I knew right away it was A.
The way he phrases it is so annoyingly good.
He does sound pretty convincing though.
We still don't know yet.
Still, having Atsushi here is reassuring.
That white ventriloquist dummy Takeuchi brought is kinda creepy, you know?
(ventriloquist)         (dummy)
He's wearing white...
It's because of the perspective
Self-proclaimed wine lover Atsushi heads to Room A, where the white ventriloquist dummy awaits.
I knew it.
So Tendo went over there.
Yeah, that's right.
That's the thing.
But sometimes one person ends up the sole winner.
That's pretty cool when it happens.
There have been a few times where someone wins the wine round all by themselves.
And a new challenger appears already.
Now, GACKT-sama.
Yes, it is GACKT-sama.
Top-tier entertainer GACKT-sama.
This time he's taking on the challenge completely alone, with no time rest between questions.
How far will he extend his personal streak of 81 consecutive wins?
No one's going to miss something this easy.
That's what he's saying people!
I haven't given my answer yet, though.
The absolute champion, GACKT-sama, starts with wine A.
Wait, the glass is different?
From ours? For real?
Looks like it.
The glass is different
Please focus on GACKT's wine glass.
That's his own glass, right?
Yes, we have him bring it every year.
Because it's his personal glass.
It's his Dragon Glass.
He gently swirls his special glass and carefully checks the aroma.
Then slowly, he sips with his elevated palate...
Chu
Chu chu
Chu chu chu
...delicately tasting every nuance.
Right.
Now all eyes are on Wine B.
He gives this one a faint swirl as well and checks the bouquet.
Do you really have to lift it up that high?
To see it in the light or something?
Then, quite casually, he takes a sip.
GACKT's verdict is...
Okay.
Which one did he pick?
B was fast.
Just from one sip.
This year as well...
To keep other teams from relaxing as soon as GACKT picks his answer,
we've prepared a special room.
We won't say which one GACKT chose yet
We'll only explain why he chose his answer.
Did he already know about this rare wine?
There are a few vintages in history that are called so-called "godly years."
And this '47 is said to be a truly miraculous year.
But...
Because of the extreme heat,
the acidity
has
basically disappeared.
The acidity disappeared?
For a wine that's been aged this long,
of course the quality is high,
but compared to other La Missions, it doesn't quite reach that level.
He's insanely knowledgeable.
On the other bottle,
the clusters are
rougher compared to La Mission.
You can tell which one is La Mission...
just by looking at it.
No way!
That's amazing.
He's unbelievable.
How was that, hearing GACKT's explanation just now?
He talked about the heatwave continuing and all that,
so I feel a bit more confident in my own choice.
Seriously?
GACKT, currently on a personal streak of 81 straight wins.
Which wine did he choose, A or B?
(nuts counter)
Next up...
Here they come.
Do your best!
Kei Inoo
not only an idol in Hey! Say! JUMP but also drawing attention for his acting.
Mitsuomi Takahashi
A top actor who plays a wide range of roles and leaves a strong impression in many works.
How are you with wine?
I don't drink that much wine, but last year in France I had some vintage wines...
including a bottle from the year Hey! Say! JUMP debuted, which I got to try.
So if we're talking in that general direction, I think I can probably guess it.
You might nail this.
And Mitsu-san, how about you?
Well, in the drama '50-Minute Lover,'
there are scenes where I drink wine,
so in that sense I've done some studying as well,
I've got this.
Thank you for that very ordinary comment.
You were talking like you were about to say something amazing, you know.
First, let's start with Wine A, which everyone except Tendo chose.
(gulp)
He's drinking a lot.
Is he ok?
Whoa, whoa, you don't have to finish the whole thing.
The lead of the new drama is the playful type who just gulps it all down.
He really is drinking the whole thing.
And the answer they gave is...
Ready, set...
Oh!
They all matched!
Whoa.
Whoa, is that really it...?
(still confident)
The aroma was already totally different right here.
Yeah, completely different.
I didn't even need it brought all the way over.
This one has overwhelming depth,
and this unique, slightly bitter astringency,
and that part really makes you feel its history.
Tendo, you look like you're about to cry right now.
About to cry?
Yeah, pretty much.
It's her first time, you know.
But it's okay.
She might end up being the only one who got it right.
Yeah, a solo victory.
Tendo~!
You'll be fine.
Unlike "lonely Tendo," in the other room...
more and more people are gathering.
Oh!
Excuse us.
Thank goodness.
With this many people here, it's reassuring.
But Tendo is insanely confident.
Oh right, Tendo's the only one in the other room.
That's true.
Tendo, with unshakable confidence.
Will she pull off a brilliant solo victory?
Next up,
Here they come!
They’re here!
Kis-My-Ft2!
From Kis-My-Ft2,
Daisuke Fujigaya,
Toshiya Miyata,
and Yokoo Wataru
Top idols whose overwhelming live performances have always captivated fans,
first-rank entertainers highly praised for their solo work in films and dramas.
We nailed it last time. We really did.
We got it right.
In Kis-My-Ft2, the three older members...
I see.
But even with three of you, you really can end up split.
Still, we’ll probably decide fast without disagreeing,
and hit the answer right away.
We’re top-tier, after all.
Kis-My-Ft2 sound confident about wine. They start with glass A.
Yokoo already knows, I can tell.
Seriously?
Or maybe he really doesn’t.
Wait, which is it then?
Yokoo sometimes makes that face even when he has no idea.
I don’t know.
Does Yokoo actually know the answer?
What are you doing?
What are you doing!
What happened?
It went down the wrong way.
Careful there.
Now that I've hit forty.
This still-active idol is choking and coughing like an old man.
The answer the three of them come up with is...
Ready, set
A!
You’re kidding!
They split.
We’ve got a split decision.
Then let's just go with A.
Yeah, let's make it A.
They split.
(friends coming?)
The smell of A was stronger
But I felt B went down easier.
But wasn't he coughing?
Ok let's go for A
Because I coughed
Because of that you changed you mind?
She must be uncomfortable right now
It's ok
Kis-my-Ft2 also picked A.
It seems A is the right answer.
Everyone, lock in your answers.
Whoa!
Thank goodness.
What a relief.
Man...
Looks like A has the edge.
(killing time)
And lastly,
Thanks for having us
Here we are, the final round.
From Fruits Zipper,
Suzuka Chinsei, Karen Matsumoto, and Yui Sakurai!
With catchy songs and razor-sharp dance moves,
they've shot to nationwide fame,
and just yesterday made their first appearance on the legendary New Year's Eve show, Kouhaku Uta Gassen.
So, how about wine?
I love wine.
You do?
Yeah, if everyone just goes with what I say, we should be fine.
So even if you split, everyone should side with you, right?
I've actually never had wine before.
So I'm kind of like, What do I even do?'
But I figured maybe I should just pick whichever one tastes better.
Exactly!
Wait, really? That works?
Yay!
Alright then.
The confident Chinsei stands in the center,
with Matsumoto, trying wine for the very first time,
Will beginner's luck strike?
One of you isn't drinking, right?
That's right, I'm not.
I don't drink alcohol at all.
This is literally her first time ever.
Wine really is a first in her life.
...seems first time
Next, they try wine B, which only Tendo has chosen so far.
Which one will the three of them choose?
You guys are ok?
Their final answer is...
Ready, and
A!
Ohh!
(could be in trouble)
Hard to believe that's their first time drinking it.
That's impressive!
But that almost makes me more nervous.
Yeah, seriously.
I see... is everyone okay with that?
When I drank B, I thought it smelled a bit off, so I figured A was the real one.
Simple.
Super concise.
Easy to understand.
Tendo-san.
(tired of waiting)
You are practically leaning over.
I feel incredibly awful right now.
It is okay, Tendo-san.
Fruits Zipper, who were totally in sync, also chose A.
Ready, and...
Oh, there are people over there too.
This is no time to be saying 'Oh, there are people over there too.'
Thank you all for your patience.
the correct answer will be the room the Ranking Master goes into.
Please wait just a little longer.
Fork in Fate: time for the results.
Here we are.
Alright then, let us open the door to the correct room.
Please.
The correct answer is...
Is it A,
or is B not to be underestimated?
Huh?
Seriously?
The correct answer is A.
In Check 1, the 1-million-yen wine was A.
You were the only one who got it wrong.
It is insanely awkward right now.
We are a team, you know.
To be honest, I was leaning toward A.
The correct A was Château La Mission Haut-Brion.
GACKT currently has an 81-win personal streak.
Will he choose the correct A and extend his winning streak?
Fork in Fate: GACKT's reveal.
Here we go.
So, which side is GACKT on?
Did GACKT get it right?
Let us find out.
Look.
Excellent!
This time...
this was the easiest challenge of all time
How many nuts did you eat?!
I was waiting a long time
(nut counter)
Relaxed enough to savor his nuts, his winning streak now reaches 82.
GACKT gets off to a fantastic rocket start in 2026 as well.
Everyone else, except Tendo Emiko, splendidly kept their top-tier rating.
Of course, the team that got it wrong will be treated accordingly.
The people who answered correctly are back.
These are the ones who guessed the 1-million-yen wine.
GACKT, 82 straight wins.
Congratulations.
That was outstanding.
Out of 8 groups, 7 got it right.
Now, the ones who were wrong...
To the person who made a mistake...
Please, come on in.
Huh, we are going in from there?
Huh?
What ...?
Crawling?
Only one person got it wrong.
Here comes Tendo-san.
That is a grapevine branch.
Please take that with you and return to your seat.
That was rough, huh?
Fumi-san, I am sorry.
No, it is totally fine.
But you know...
That was an awful time for you, was it not, Tendo-san?
Do you have to put it like that?
Hurry up and take off those slippers.
Thank you.
Oh, don't need these...
thanks for your hard work.
She even threw the slippers.
Why throw the slippers?
Now, for the next check...
Here is the second check.
It is 'tate' choreographed sword-fighting.
'Tate' is, in plays and films...
the term for choreographed fighting scenes mainly using swords.
It demands high-level skills: speed, intensity, acting ability...
This time, we want you to judge the performances of the people being cut down in tate.
For Check 2: tate
We have the cooperation of Japan Action Enterprise.
It was founded by international star Shinichi Chiba in 1970
and is a prestigious school that has trained action stars, including Hiroyuki Sanada in the past.
The correct answer is this top-tier period-drama tate group, each with over 30 years of experience.
These four have appeared in famed period dramas like the Taiga series,
'Abarenbo Shogun', 'Onihei', 'Hankacho', 'Mito Komon', and many more.
Between the four of them, they have been 'cut down'
over 20,000 times,
making them superhuman-level victims.
And to compare, the other side is a young tate group with much less period-drama experience.
They are gradually building experience and, between the four of them, have been cut about 800 times.
Oh wow... that's still a lot of times!
This time, it will be set up like a period-drama episode,
and you will compare the two tate performances.
We have invited the big bad boss who leads these doomed underlings.
Here he is. Please come in.
This is Satoshi Jinbo.
Jinbo-san has appeared in many period dramas,
including year-long historical epics.
Jinbo, how was it for you doing these things again?
Doing stage combat again really reminded me how deep and complex it is.
And now, the boss who takes down Jinbo's gang of villains, the star of today's show...
Ryuji Harada.
You all know Mr. Harada, ...
He played Sukesan in 'Mito Komon', among many other roles,
and has appeared in countless period dramas.
Seike Kazuto from Toei Tsurugikai, who has supervised sword-fighting choreography on many period dramas,
has said this about him:
'No one else can move at that speed.'
and that he has an aesthetic sense that really sets him apart from other actors.
He is showered with praise.
They say he is one of the top five period-drama actors for sword-fighting work.
See? It turned out just like I taught you, right?
That is true.
Thank you.
How did it feel actually doing it this time?
I think in stage combat the one who gets cut has the more important role.
I see.
More important than the one doing the cutting, you mean?
The people being tested are these familiar faces.
For them, telling top-level sword-fighting apart should be an easy question.
Alright, representatives, please step forward.
They will be watching this check in groups, all at the same time.
We will start with these four groups.
Mao Daichi, a legendary top star of the Takarazuka Revue and still a first-class entertainer on the front lines.
Back in my Takarazuka days I did play the one doing the cutting,
but being the one who gets cut is a bit...
You need to study that side of it.
Emiko Kaminuma, celebrating the 55th anniversary of her debut this year,
a Kansai-based host and singer, currently ranked as a mid-level celebrity on this show.
Sorry to bring up such an old story,
but 48 years ago...
That was rude...
I used to go to Uzuno-san's film studio every single week.
You honestly do not remember that, do you?
I do remember!
You remember things from when you were young really well.
Better than remembering what you ate yesterday.
Koda Kumi
She has three albums which sold over 1 million copies.
A top rated artist in Japan who has won numerous awards.
I have been doing traditional dance since I was three.
I have also had the chance to perform sword dances,
so I really feel I cannot afford to get this wrong.
I absolutely want to get the right answer.
It is just that...
When you start saying things like 'it is just that' to everyone...
I am afraid I will get dazzled by how beautiful the one doing the cutting looks.
The person swinging the sword, I mean.
Kis-My-Ft2.
Hamamori Yuta, Kento Senga, and Takashi Nikaido.
A top idol group whose New Year countdown concert was a huge success.
We once had people from Japan Action Enterprise
personally teach us.
They said you cannot make it look good unless,
even as the one getting cut, you put yourself in the cutter's position.
But you are an idiot, you think such about such deep things?
Of course!
I will be cut in absolutely perfect fashion.
Which one is Kirara - the veteran with 30 years of stage combat experience? A or B?
This challenge is presented as a period-drama scene, with acting before and after the fight.
Please consider it together with us.
If you want a closer look, you can come up to around here.
If you are fine where you are, you can stay put.
First, fight A.
Princess...
the mountain path is rough from here. I must ask you to leave the carriage and walk.
If we do not hurry, the Hamada clan's men may catch up with us.
(heroine at 3pm comedian Kanade)
Ryuji, I am sorry to keep causing you such hardship.
Think nothing of it. Come, let us go.
Princess Kanade, you have nowhere left to run.
Damn, they have cut us off.
I will not let you lay a single finger on the princess.
Are you alright?
Leave this to me.
Ryuji...
Your fate is sealed.
Men, to me!
On my life,
I will take the princess back!
Men, attack!
As expected of you, Ryuji.
But do not think this is the end.
Ryuji..
That's was excellent!
Still...
there might be more
We must hurry on.
Walk?
Please.
You could really feel that 'I am ready to die' emotion there.
They took those blows beautifully.
Next is fight B.
We start from the ninja's entrance.
Ryuji!
Your fate is sealed.
Men, to me!
I will get the princess back, even if it costs me my life!
Men!
Attack!
Impressive as always, Ryuji
But don't think it's over yet.
What the hell?
So annoying.
Ryuji! Thank you so much!
There might be still enemies hiding.
Let's hurry on.
Right.
You took too long!
Hahaha... took too long!
The acting in the second half dragged on a bit too long...
Yeah, kinda.
Jun, by the way, which one do you think it is?
In A, it felt like they were acting in a way that made it easier for Harada-san to land the cut.
And you two from Fruits Zipper, which do you think it was?
I thought it was team B.
I thought it was B as well.
We're split on this one.
with the three of us split like this...
I was leaning toward A.
The two next to me were both saying B.
Tendo-san...
I've also done period dramas, actually,
so I think it was B.
When they delivered that slash,
the way they slowly staggered back,
it really looked like they'd been cut through the torso.
With A I somehow got more of a dynamic feel.
So A. I'm going with A.
Got it.
Takeshi, what about you?
B.
And you?
Well, A definitely had better tempo and flowed more smoothly,
but my eyes kept going to B's opponent and the way they handled the distance,
so that's why I'm choosing B
Understood.
So which was it for Kirara, the veteran with thirty years in the business: A or B?
First up, Daichi Mao, who has sword-fighting experience from her Takarazuka days.
Here we go.
Which way will Dai-san go?
Her answer is...
Oh, you can really see Dai-san's eye for this.
You're in agreement.
Everyone's teamwork is really in sync,
and even when I watched them lying there after being cut,
there was absolutely no sense of them breathing,
which I thought was amazing.
Exactly.
I see.
We on set didn't even notice that.
You focus on totally different things.
Wonderful.
Daichi Mao chooses B.
She wants to somehow make up for her partner Tendo's mistake.
Ordinary Emi Kaminuma.
I really want to keep my status as a 'normal celebrity'.
Her answer is...
B.
From the setup you could see they were fully committed to being the one who gets cut down.
I thought, wow, that's what a real veteran looks like.
I'm confident.
Thank you very much.
She never forgets to say thank you, appreciating everything
She is headed to the room Daichi Mao is waiting in: B
Thank...you...so...much
Definitely B
Koda Kumi has been doing kenbu since 3 years old
Here she comes
Can she remain 1st class?
Correct answer is...
B.
Another B.
The streak continues.
Looking at the lingering aftereffect once they'd been cut,
I felt like they really paid attention to the details.
Her opinion's a little different from Hiromi-sama's, though.
True.
We'll see which way it goes.
Since both of you were saying B,
I kind of started remembering it that way too.
So, B.
Not that my own reactions have anything to do with it.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Hiromi-san, that has absolutely nothing to do with it though.
So it's the opposite of Hiromi Go.
Takada also chooses B.
Whoa.
All right!
I thought if Taishi-san was in there, then B had to be OK.
Because you two are here I have confidence
Kis-My-Ft2 have been trained directly by the professional group
Here comes...
Which will they pick?
Kis-My-Ft2 split their answer last time...
This one cannot be wrong
split
A was smooth...wasn't it?
For real?
What really decided it for me
was how they left a wide acting area
for the showdown between Jimbo-san and Harada-san.
B.
You were really watching closely.
I'm the only one left, so I'll go with B to match you.
This really felt like B to me, you could hear it in their voice, it was amazing.
That's important.
All right, I'll make this one B.
This really brings back how we used to learn it, huh.
Kis-My also chose B.
Off to Room B, where the lovely ladies are waiting.
Right!?
So far, everyone has picked B.
So which one is actually correct?
Check No. 2: Swordplay.
Up to this point, everyone has gone with B.
Next up, these four groups will take the test.
Kimura Tae.
She plays everything from serious roles to comedy.
A top-tier actor, famous as a brilliant supporting performer.
People think I move really slowly all the time, but...
They once asked me if I wanted to join the Japan Action Club.
I kind of got scouted for it.
They said, 'You've got talent, why not join?'
For real?
You really do give off that slow, laid-back vibe though.
But I can actually move fast.
FRUITS ZIPPER.
Nakagawa Runa.
Manaka Mana.
With a total number of TikTok views that's just insane,
they're a top idol group on a whole different level.
Since we dance and perform a lot,
I think we should look at how dynamic
their movements are and all that.
That's what I'm thinking.
Yeah.
Batteries.
They were runners-up at the M-1 Grand Prix the year before last and blew up nationwide.
Top-class entertainers who embody both M-1-level comedy and mainstream appeal.
We've seen a lot in theaters too,
like tons of people getting slashed in skits and stuff.
There's just one thing I'm a bit worried about.
Right at the beginning, when it first came up on screen,
Ace was like, 'How are you even supposed to read that kanji?'
I've never really seen those characters before.
And GACKT, currently on an 82-game personal winning streak,
has appeared in many period dramas, including historical epics.
The people I've gone up against in sword-fighting scenes have all been first-rate pros.
Right.
So there's no mistaking it.
Is that so?
You're confident about this one too?
Did you eat before coming here?
You could speak up a bit more, you know.
You're really, uh, something today.
You're being super harsh to literally everyone.
No, I'm not.
First, the swordplay team A.
For everyone watching at home,
let us share some tips on how to spot the correct one.
If they're just standing there getting cut, they're still green.
The veterans rush in to attack and then get cut down themselves.
They also have the skill to move in perfect sync so the lead can strike at just the right moment.
Keeping that in mind, watch closely.
Men, attack!
And the evil boss is safely taken down as well.
Next, swordplay team B.
Face me!
Men, charge!
The evil boss held out stubbornly until the very end, but was finally defeated.
We're in the middle of a special here!
But this is really tough, isn't it?
Yeah, super hard.
First, GACKT, who just extended his winning streak to 82.
How did he arrive at his answer this time?
Just talking about the timing of getting cut,
the veterans are better at matching their timing.
They don't sit there and wait, you know?
Instead of waiting for the strike
and then trying to match it themselves,
they have the skill to let getting cut happen as a completely natural flow.
Once again, GACKT is totally composed.
So which did he choose, A or B?
And actress Kimura Tae, who's secretly quick on her feet,
was she able to pick out the first-rate sword fighters?
Ah, right now, Mizu-chan...
What answer did you give?
Ready, set...
Looks like we're split.
Yeah,they're divided.
They split on this one.
The part where they came down from the roof and rolled along the ground,
that bit made me think A as well.
With A, I really felt that veteran presence.
The B team felt fresher, like they were younger.
I'm going with A.
Really?
Let's choose A.
You're sure about that?
Yeah, that moment made me think, 'Oh, it's probably that side,' too.
So we ended up disagreeing with Mitsuumi-sama, who's still left in.
Yeah.
They decide to respect the opinion of Ino, star of the new drama,
And now, for the first time here, they pick A.
Heading into an empty room.
There's no one here.
Oh crap.
(suddenly anxious)
No way!
Huh? What? Seriously?
You have correct eyes yes?
Yeah, this is kind of scary, but I thought it was A
These three are top-tier idols from FRUITS ZIPPER, with a Tokyo Dome concert coming up next month.
All right, here we go.
And the answer they chose is...
Same!
Whoa, we're kind of split on this one, but...
Huh?
There’s nothing to argue about now, everyone picked A.
The voice, like, the deepness to it.
Yeah, totally.
Their voice just kind of...
That part really felt weighty, you know? Like it had gravitas.
That veteran vibe.
So it might be A
Man, when it gets like this I honestly have no idea anymore.
FRUITS ZIPPER, who now also act on the side, all unanimously chose A.
At this point, the A room has suddenly gotten packed.
Ready, and...
The teams are split!
(even more anxious)
We're divided.
Split decision.
You’re kidding.
He's eating something again
Why do we have to watch this?
The eating scene.
Batteries cannot afford to blow it in front of their great senior, Atsushi.
I hope they all match.
What did they choose?
One, two...
Oh!
Whaaat!
Nice, they matched.
For real?
With B, it honestly felt like you could almost see the blood.
That intense?
Yeah, it was that sharp, that powerful.
The realism, or rather the impact, too.
B definitely had more of that.
They were clearly different.
But in the end, it's up to the people on set.
All right, so you two are going with B.
The two from Batteries choose B, a different answer from senior Atsushi.
I'm so awkward at this, first time going through this door.
Ohh.
Thank goodness.
What a relief.
So glad.
(now risky)
You’ve got to be kidding.
If we can win with this...
So which one is correct, A or B?
Stand by for the answer.
Is it A, or is it B?
The fateful crossroads: time for the results.
All right, here we are.
Here it comes.
It's here, it's here!
This is intense.
Please
We will now open the door to the correct room.
This is nerve-racking.
Please...
The correct answer is...
The correct answer was B.
There was a little bit of a fake-out in there.
Nice faking!
As expected of you.
They were completely different.
Shock!
No way!
Will the ever-confident GACKT-sama choose the correct B and extend his annual winning streak?
The fateful crossroads: GACKT's answer.
Well, Gak-chan is probably in there too...
Let's find out. Okay, here we go.
All right, he's in.
Wow, that's insane.
This was way too easy.
Yeah, it was ridiculously easy.
Weren't there a ton of correct-choosers this time?
But the A side had quite a few too.
There are like three groups in there.
Seriously?
Yeah, that’s pretty bad.
GACKT-sama nails it with ease and reaches 83 straight wins.
We have two teams who did pretty terribly, though.
Up next, an even more disastrous incident explodes onto the scene.
Okay, all the players who got it right have returned.
Thanks for your hard work.
Welcomed by Mr. Harada, Mr. Ichio, Mr. Katate, and our first-class troupe, the winners are making their entrance.
Congratulations.
You all did brilliantly.
And now, for those who got it wrong...
Wrong-answer team, come on in.
Instead of applause,
this time you'll be welcomed with cold stares from Harada-san, Jimbo-san, Kanade-san, and our top-tier squad.
So frustrating.
Our incorrect-answer group has returned.
When this many groups get it right, you have to say the professionals live up to their reputation.
Once you actually go up against the veterans, you can really tell they're on a different level.
I see.
You dragged it out too long.
Sorry about that.
We really didn't need you
What do you mean?
Alright, everyone,
thank you for all your hard work.
Thank you very much.