***Subtitles generated by Whisper V3 translated by GPT5.4 edited by Ardarvin & Mayumi***
Once again, only on TVer, we're showing what happened before the taping
with Hamada and Hirodo doing their pre-show check.
Hamada-san, happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
This time as well, of course, it'll be streaming on TVer.
So let’s nail it right now.
Yeah, of course we will.
Our first New Year challenge is wine.
The correct one is a top-class wine that goes for 1 million yen a bottle at luxury hotels.
They will compare it against a 5,000-yen wine.
By the way, in the main show, seven pairs got it right.
Only veteran singer Tendo Yoshimi got it wrong.
I really thought I had it right, you know.
And of course, this man, needless to say, chose correctly.
We’re still doing wine, huh?
Forever.
Miyata-san, you probably didn’t notice, but the moment the wine came out you crossed your legs.
That’s real confidence, Hamada-san.
Still doing this, huh.
Exactly. First up, the correct one: the 1-million-yen wine.
Do you really need to look that close?
I look like Okahachiro (old-school Kansai comedian)
Next, B: the 5,000-yen wine.
And the answer they chose is...
That turned out well.
I kind of don’t like that our answers match.
There’s that 'because it’s aged' thing.
How should I put it...
Like, over a long time it’s been...
sitting in the barrel, soaking in
'Rested in the barrel' wine.
Yeah, yeah, something like that.
I felt like that kind of aroma just slid right in.
What about you?
The smell when they poured it,
it was obviously...
The aroma the moment the wine was poured was overwhelmingly better.
Make sure you count that, okay? How many comments he steals from me.
OK!
Let’s make 2026 a really good year.
The correct answer is
A.
Nice.
That’s really good.
2026 is going to be different.
With that correct answer, they stay top-class.
Sounds like 2026 is off to a good start, right?
The second challenge is tate sword-fighting.
The correct answer is B: an elite tate troupe with over 30 years of experience and more than 20,000 stage slashes.
And the wrong one, A, was a young tate troupe with much less experience.
On a question an actor absolutely shouldn’t miss,
Tae Kimura got it wrong.
And proved too difficult for current idols FRUITS ZIPPER and Hey! Say! JUMP.
This segment is presented as a period-drama-style mini story.
The lead, fleeing with the princess from evil pursuers, is played by Ryuji Harada.
Se’s basically a regular on this show now.
With that princess, you could just leave her behind, couldn’t you?
Ryuji, I am sorry to always burden you so.
Come, let us go.
The evil boss targeting the princess is played by veteran actor Satoshi Jimbo.
Ryuji, your fate is sealed.
First, the wrong answer, A.
Next up the professionals...
As I expected Ryuji
But do not think it ends here.
He very stubborn
What are you even doing?
So annoying
It's too long!
Please die already!
Jinbo-san is taking too long
...so we will skip the ending
Their answer is...
We are matched
Why did you pick B?
They kept making sounds and reacting the whole time,
it wasn’t just, 'get cut and fall down.'
In all the other moments too,
the way they stayed in character was impressive.
I felt there was a real depth to it.
With B, from the moment they appeared,
how to say...
there was this sense of ease, of being used to it.
Group A came out all hyped up and excited.
Like, 'Let’s do our best!'
You said it.
This is pure Hamada logic.
A just rushed in, 'Bam!'
B wasn’t especially fast, just solid and steady.
But, you know, the thing we can’t tell is,
they might be doing that on purpose, right?
Ok shall we reveal the correct answer?
The correct answer is...
B.
That makes two.
Amazing.
We’re on a roll.
All right, all right.
Wow, splendid! Two correct answers in a row.
Maybe they'll manage to stay first-class till the very end.
Check 3: Octet Orchestra
A showdown over their true value.
The correct choice is the most expensive in the show's history.
World-famous instruments worth over 10 billion yen in total.
The real highlight: this is its very first public appearance in Japan.
The Stradivarius 'Corbett'.
They'll compare it with a hobby-level instrument.
In the main show,
If a musician gets this one wrong,
they should really just retire.
Retire?!
With their careers on the line in this test,
an incredible six pairs got it wrong.
The few who did get it right...
...burst into tears of joy.
That would mean this is the year Koda Kumi retires.
No, seriously.
First, the correct one, A.
The instruments worth over 10 billion yen.
Next, the wrong choice: the hobby-level instrument.
This is rough...
Their answer was...
Split.
Split, huh?
Oh? Why's that?
I went with the classic theory for this one.
'A' felt like it was trying too hard, right?
There it is.
(he says this every time)
The high notes sounded really piercing, you know?
Yeah, kind of.
Whereas this one...
...just flowed so naturally.
I felt like it played really beautifully.
'A' had a 'hysterical' quality
'Hysterical.'
So I chose this one.
How about you?
One decisive thing was the final 'jaaan' chord.
The way it rang out afterwards, this one had more...
...you could feel its age.
It just felt more high-end.
Seriously?
At the end?
Wait, really?
(silently switches)
Yeah.
Wait.. wait.. wait...
please stop!
Really!?
The correct answer is...
I want to keep top tier
A.
So in the end...
For music questions you always say who is doing their best
Please stop this theory
Too bad, Hama-chan, you couldn't stay in the top rank.
Get it right next time, okay?
The fourth test is Michelin-star chefs.
The correct answer is C: Chef Matsumoto of La Paix in Nihonbashi, Tokyo.
A top restaurant with one Michelin star for eight years straight.
This time we had Chef Matsumoto make classic Western-style dishes: beef stew and doria.
In the main show, four pairs got it right.
Wrong answer A was a Western-style restaurant in Nippori, Tokyo,
run by two brothers, aged 82 and 73:
Chefs Tadao Sato and Eiji Sato.
We also had the Sato brothers make both dishes.
Since doria isn't on their menu,
it was their first time making it since they opened.
In the main show, three pairs ended up picking the neighborhood restaurant.
ahhh I made a mistake!
And the dreaded two-rank drop,
the 'absolutely no good' choice is Chef Hamada, who has fooled 36 people so far.
To be honest, Hamada-san's cooking is
actually really good.
Even GACKT raves about him,
Chef Hamada make beef stew and doria as well.
In the main show, everyone in FRUITS ZIPPER except one member picked Chef Hamada.
These kids are so sweet.
Off they go to the 'Absolutely No Good' room.
This time Hamada will eat the beef stew, and Hirodo-sama will have the doria.
First, the wrong answer: the neighborhood restaurant's flavor.
If you refuse we have to stop filming
Next, the two-rank drop: Chef Hamada's dish.
You can at least recognize your own cooking, right?
And finally, the correct one:
Chef Matsumoto's dish from La Paix, Nihonbashi.
Their answer is...
Ah.
It's pretty amazing to agree when there are three choices.
This one was insanely good.
That was the beef stew, right?
The tenderness of the meat,
and when you eat it, the slight hint of wine in the sauce...
...just gently wafts up through your nose.
It has to be A, no question.
I had the doria,
and A was overwhelmingly creamier.
I think B was probably Hamada-san.
So which one do you think was yours?
The definitely don't pick Hamada-san's cooking?
Which is your beef stew?
C.
Yeah, I figured.
Which would mean that, after all...
Then this one is definitely...
If he picked his own...
No way that would happen.
All right, time for the results.
The correct answer is
C.
Whoa, hold on.
C was Michelin-starred?
Mine is B.
That's right...
'A' was crazy good.
It was delicious.
Simple good food
Ah, yes.
Whoa both were wrong.
Looks like our dopey-MC era is going strong in 2026 too.
The fifth test is the orchestra.
The correct pro is the Japan Century Symphony Orchestra.
One of Japan's leading musicians.
Hisaishi Jo-san fell in love with their performance,
and became their music director in April 2025.
They will be compared with a university orchestra.
On vocals, Shigeru Matsuzaki.
Wait, seriously?
He'll be singing 'Ai no Memory'.
Of course he is.
FRUITS ZIPPER's look-alikes are taking on this round.
If they don't pick the right one, they vanish instantly.
You sure about this?
In the end, 1 pair chose A and 6 pairs chose B.
FRUITS ZIPPER are in room B. So, is B the right answer?
A is correct!
FRUITS ZIPPER disappeared with one question still to go.
They've vanished.
By the way, what about this person?
Nicely done, that's correct!
That was really hard.
So what's your musical theory behind that?
The Japan Century Symphony and Kyoto University's symphony orchestra
are both insanely high quality,
so honestly, telling you to judge just from the performance
is pretty tough, in my opinion.
But if you flip it and ask instead which one
lets Mr. Matsuzaki really sing the way he wants to,
then once you search for that, it's honestly obvious at a glance,
you can tell right away.
Can Hamada and Hiroto pick the correct one?
First, here is the correct one.
Next, the incorrect B version.
Even on the day I turn into a star,
I will never part from you.
Shigeru, Akira, you're in the way!
Their answer is...
Doesn't it feel like B supported Mr. Matsuzaki's singing more?
That's right.
It's not that this performance here is worse.
But this one was way easier to sing with,
he was singing really comfortably.
With this one,
I had to pretend he was singing comfortably.
The one where he sounded more at ease was B
(same theory as GACKT but incorrect)
In terms of cohesion and scale and all that,
Hmm, so the right answer is...
Come on
Come on.
A.
There goes that logic.
Yeah.
Wow, this is really tough.
Was there like a four or five hour gap between singing A and B?
No, not at all.
No, for A he just jumped straight in, like, 'Here we gooo,'
even though my voice isn't warmed up yet, kind of thing.
His voice was totally fine.
This one felt like he had a rest in between,
so he could belt out 'Beautiful life',
But it's not how Mr. Matsuzaki did...
You think so?
Yeah.
Shut up!
Right?
I thought he sang comfortably,
which made the whole performance better.
Wow.
Yeah, this one is a bit...
And with that, they drop down one rank together.
Being all buddy-buddy doesn't help.
Now finish it off with a perfect answer on the last one, okay?
The final test is shabu-shabu.
The correct one is from a long-established restaurant in Tokyo's Ningyocho with over 100 years of history,
Hiyama's Yonezawa beef shabu-shabu.
This time, both of the wrong ones are 'no way' options and you disappear the moment you pick them.
They'll be compared with pork and wild boar.
In the main show, three pairs managed to get it right,
but two people with dumb tongues actually mixed up beef and pork.
Go Hiromi, who celebrates his 55th anniversary next year, chose pork
and went, 'Japan!'
And... gone.
And Atsushi Tamura as well...
The correct answer is A.
(not worth showing)
On the other hand...
Boar!
She can't tell the difference between beef and wild boar
By the way, GACKT's result...
Knew it.
Once again, a perfect score: that makes 87 straight wins.
It's beef, pork, and boar, right?
Are you kidding me?
If you don't pick the right one, you disappear on the spot.
They are different meats
Yeah, they're different types.
Ah, damn it.
First up, A.
I don't need
If you pick this, you will disappear.
Next, the correct one, B: Yonezawa beef shabu-shabu.
And finally, C: wild boar.
Whoever picked this is an idiot.
They will have a disciplinary meeting after the taping.
All right, please take off your eye masks.
Okay, okay.
Beef, pork, boar? I say beef.
Just a moment.
The answers you gave are...
Ready, set...
Whoa!
I’m so over this, seriously.
I just hate it when our answers split like this.
Excuse me, senpai, can I say something?
There is no way it’s B.
I’m sorry, I’m sorry, I mean it.
Seriously.
B is the boar.
For real.
No, I’m absolutely sure.
Which one’s the boar?
This one. (picks up C)
A is pork
B is boar, and A is pork
This is pork. (picks up A)
This is beef, and this is boar.
I see. Then I’ll reveal the pork first.
It’s A.
See, that’s what I was saying!
I’ve been telling you that!
But I’m telling you, B is the boar.
So it’s either the right answer or the boar, yeah?
All right, I’ll take it. Thank you very much.
Our totally confident 'Boar' Ayumi Hirodo is about to lose.
The correct answer is
B.
Wait, wait, wait! Hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wild boar!
Scary, scary...
Uncool!
Uncool.
What should I do?
I want to slap you
Excuse me, sorry, you’re too loud!
Don’t be wandering around outside at New Years
This is bad!
I’m not even in the shot, am I?
People are gonna call you 'Little Boar,' you know.
Out on the street.
All right, we’re good. Thank you.
Honestly, jokes aside, I really thought C was beef
No, no, for real.
Okay, let’s go get the guests
Thank you very much.
No, I honestly thought so.