***Subtitles generated by Whisper V3 translated by GPT5.4 edited by Ardarvin & Mayumi***
Alright, let's move on to the next test.
Here is the fifth test.
Check 5: Orchestra
You can hear everyone buzzing already.
You'll be comparing a 24-piece professional orchestra with an amateur one.
Check 5: Orchestra
Our professional orchestra is the Japan Century Symphony Orchestra.
They were founded in 1989.
and give over 200 performances a year, all of them highly praised.
They have won numerous awards and are among Japan's leading orchestras.
Shigemasa Hisai took over as music director last April.
On the amateur side, from a university that has produced multiple Nobel laureates,
we have the Kyoto University Symphony Orchestra, from Japan's top-level university.
This student orchestra boasts one of the longest histories, celebrating its 110th anniversary this year.
On the 15th and 17th of this month, they'll be sharing the stage with a concertmaster who has long led Japan's classical music scene,
the distinguished Fuminori Shinozaki.
They are a highly prestigious orchestra.
And on top of that, we'll have a vocalist to add even more color to the performance.
The singer is this man.
Shigeru Matsuzaki, known for the song 'Utsukushii Jinsei' (Beautiful Life).
No, really, this is something else.
Are we seriously pitting the pros against amateurs here?
But the people here today who work in music,
there's no way they'll get this wrong.
Of course not.
Yeah, obviously.
I think Shigeru's kind of bothersome.
I'm always bothersome, to be fair.
So, Masaki, please introduce our three representatives.
If you would.
Now then, let's announce the chosen representatives.
From Team 85-Win Streak, we have GACKT-sama.
From Team Tendo, it's Yoshimi Tendo-chan.
And from Team FRUITS ZIPPER, the ones who look like Chinzei, Nakagawa, and Manaka.
And these are the rest of our representatives.
Not just the FRUITS ZIPPER lookalikes,
the other teams had better stand their ground or things could get messy.
Representatives, please head to the standby room.
The hospitality in the standby rooms changes wildly depending on your rank.
What is this?
Just broth.
Broth?
Only the liquid, nothing in it.
They even took out all the contents.
First up, these five pairs.
Can they pick out the truly first-rate sound behind Shigeru Matsuzaki's singing?
A live, in-studio performance by two orchestras.
Everyone at home, please think along with us.
Orchestra A.
The sweet remnants of love
You...
linger
With that angelic smile
time comes to a halt.
Oh beautiful life, endless joy,
I give this beating of my heart to you.
What truly matters in this world
is that we love one another,
and you are the one who shows me that.
Beautiful life, endless joy,
I offer my heartbeat to you.
Even when the day comes for us to leave this world
and become stars in the sky
I will never be apart from you.
He's annoying right?
He's Shigeru! Show respect!
Now B orchestra
The sweet remnants of love
You ... linger
With that angelic smile
time comes to a halt.
Oh beautiful life, endless joy,
I give this beating of my heart to you.
What truly matters in this world
is that we love one another,
and you are the one who shows me that.
Oh beautiful life,
endless joy
I give this trembling of my heart to you.
Even when the day comes for us to leave this world
and become stars in the sky
I will never be apart from you.
Without getting distracted by the legendary vocals,
were they able to tell the professionals from the university students?
Was the Japan Century Symphony Orchestra playing A, or was it B?
Atsushi-san.
I figured it out right away.
Oh?
It was A.
A.
Yeah, no doubt.
The depth of sound was completely different.
More than anything, they weren't being thrown off by Shigeru.
I see.
With B, it felt like they were getting a bit tossed around by Shigeru.
Seriously?
I knew in an instant.
B.
For me it was the opposite, I felt Matsuzaki-san was more into it with B.
By the way, which one did you pick?
Same as him.
B ... seriously
Shigeru-san is in the zone
Same opinion
my heart is fluttering a bit
We are connected
How about Kumi-chan?
I think...
Why are you running the show?!
Old habit
I pick B!
We even made eye contact, remember?
For real?
And you, Yukirona-san, what do you think?
I thought it was B.
Really?
You don't have to be scared Kaminuma-san
Are you scared of me?
That's no good.
Still no correct answers today from Yoshimi Tendo.
She better not take this lightly.
Here we go.
(Kaminuma-san chooses B.)
As a professional, as an artist
I absolutely have to get this one right.
I can't miss this.
As someone who just sang on Kouhaku last night, she really can't afford to blow this.
So you agreed.
For real?
That's impressive.
The depth of sound was totally different.
Of course.
Tendo, who sings 'Do Not Underestimate Me', goes with B.
Go Hiromi also performed on Kouhaku yesterday.
He cannot miss this one.
Go, go, go!
All right, here we go.
The key is, you end up listening to his singing no matter what
Exactly.
But you have to tune that out.
You need intense focus.
It's extremely annoying!
And the answer he gives is...
B.
I guess it's B after all?
In terms of how cohesive the sound was, I'd say it's B.
I see.
Hiromi Go, who has sung with countless orchestras, also chooses B, same as Tendo.
Oh, thank goodness, I'm the same as Go-san. I'm so relieved.
Which one will 2nd tier Daichi go for?
Okay, here we go.
Ma-san.
She will definitely pick B.
I want to nail this one.
I don't know, she sounds a little unsure there.
She messed up earlier (with the Michelin check) so she's feeling a little negative,
but she will be fine.
She wants to make up for that Michelin mistake.
Was it that obvious?
See?
Seriously?
Look, look.
It felt like I was being wrapped up in the sound.
I could tell the exact moment my eyes started to well up.
Following the Kouhaku singers, the former Takarazuka top star also goes with B.
Oh, thank God I'm on the same side as Mao-san. I'm so relieved.
We ended up picking the same after all, I'm glad.
Everyone has chosen B so far... is B really the right answer?
'Pro Orchestra', is it A or B?
All right, time to reveal the correct answer to everyone in the studio.
The correct answer is...
A.
Told you.
This round is about to get rocky.
Incredibly, so far Azushi-san is the only one who got it.
The impact was completely different
The force was incredible.
(confident but incorrect)
Extra Edition! Yoshimi Tendo, Hiromi Go Retire! "We're sorry for appearing on Kohaku."
Next up, 5 dome tour regular idol group Kis-my.
Here they come
'A' please.
No matter what: A
Please give me 'A'.
Can they manage to choose the correct 'A'?
Ready, set...
Go Chinga!
Are you serious right now?
Yes, seriously B.
They're going to lose.
Use that famous confidence and stick with it!
It felt like I could listen to B for longer.
No, that's not it.
No way.
No, let's stick with B.
OK.
Sen-chan!
Sen-chan it's A!
When Tama steps up like this,
it's rare for him to say, 'Let's go with this.'
Sen-chan, what do you say?
You kind of sound like you're faking it.
Sen-chan! Last call!
Sen-chan, final answer!
Ready, and...
B.
And you are the only regular-talent ranking.
Ah, Senga couldn't hold out, and Kis-My is wrong as well, off to Room B.
Everyone is here!
With the way things are going, maybe even Gackt-sama might slip up.
I think the questions up to now have been....
the easiest in the last ten years.
Seriously?
Yeah. But this time, the Kyoto University orchestra is insanely high level.
So I think this one is actually pretty tough.
You say that, but you're going to get it right aren't you?
Well, I am Gackt, after all.
How did Gackt-sama arrive at his answer?
If you figure out in which one Matsuzaki-san
is really singing the way he wants to sing,
then honestly, it's obvious.
You can tell right away.
Was Gackt-sama able to pick A, the correct answer that no one else chose?
The B room feels like the 'correct answer' atmosphere doesn't it?
Next up are these three groups, including Fruit Chuck, who are already on their last chance.
For everyone watching at home, to make it easier to follow, we will alternate between the correct performance
and Kyoto University’s performance.
The sweet remnants of love
you...
linger
With that angelic smile
time comes to a halt
Oh, beautiful life, endless joy,
I give all the beating of this heart to you.
In this world, the only thing that truly matters is loving one another,
and you are the one who shows me that.
Oh, beautiful life,
oh, endless joy,
I offer all this fluttering in my heart to you.
Even when we leave this world on the day
And we turn into stars,
I will never part from you.
Were they able to tell which one was the correct professional performance?
It has to be B.
I’m sure of it.
You’re absolutely sure?
The two of them are desperate to hang on somehow.
All right, here we go.
Okay...
It’s A, definitely A.
Hey! Say! JUMP are actually doing a live show right now too,
backed by a full orchestra at Tokyo Dome,
we’re being allowed to perform like that,
so I can’t afford to get this wrong.
So you are going to follow him?
Yes I’ll match him on this.
Their final answer is...
Ready, set...
No way!
They split
He did say he was going to match Inoo-san.
I really can’t miss this one.
Because even tomorrow, the day after this airs,
I’ll be performing again with this very orchestra
on my back at the Dome for a live show.
He's going to lean toward Inoo-san.
I’ll follow Inoo-san’s lead.
we’ll go with A, please.
Heeey!
Yes, that’s correct!
Finally there is someone for room A!
Amazing.
Seriously amazing.
We finally have someone who got it right. Yes!
But Room A is still empty.
Aaah, gangan-gaaan!
No one’s here, no one.
They went over there!
ha..
They had a huge breakout after finishing runner-up at the M-1.
The popular comedy duo, Batteries.
All right, here they come.
Go, Batteries!
I see all kinds of rhythm-based acts at the theater too,
but this is totally different from an orchestra.
And the answer they’ve come up with is...
One, two...
B!
What are you doing?!
Seriously, what are you doing?!
Batteries!
B was clearly more powerful, wasn’t it?
Yeah, the strength of the sound,
and also, when they pulled back,
the softer side of the dynamics felt deeper to me.
Aaah...
You blew it, man.
Aaah. Team Yoshimoto has lost three in a row.
They’re just rolling further and further downhill.
This is correct.
Yes.
Good.
Good, good, good.
(confident but wrong)
What...
Is it really that split?
Seriously?
This is how Emiko and Yoshimi felt
(worried but correct)
uun
For the last pair, if they get this wrong, they’ll be out
Fruit Chuck are right on the edge.
All right, they’re up!
Do your best!
Chuck is here!
I really like musicals and go see them a lot,
so I’m pretty used to hearing orchestras.
You really think that is going to get you through this?
Whoa, that got harsh all of a sudden.
Haaah!
We still don’t know yet.
They were really careful, taking each note one by one,
and I could feel that sense of, like, 'we’re going to play this properly.'
You said earlier we should go with the minority next time.
Like, your world just keeps going, 'whoa,' and opening up more and more.
Like it just keeps expanding.
Okay, it's B then
We good with this now?
Alright, last one.
Ready, and...
B!
We don't want to disappear...
(not worth showing)
Ah, wait, we're already finished?
FRUITS ZIPPER...
Dum
They disappeared.
(not worth showing)
They vanished with one question still left.
In place of those unlucky idols, from here on...
Hollywood Zakoshisho will take on the big role with his over-the-top style.
We will not disappear.
Good! They won't disappear!
(disappointed but correct)
For real?
Fateful crossroads: time for the results.
FRUITS ZIPPER has already disappeared once, but...
Please enjoy their real nervous expressions on their actual faces.
Alright, here we are.
Please!
Please come!
Come on!
The correct answer is...
(useless prayers)
I can still perform tomorrow!
(disappear) (not worth showing)
Sen-chan's face!
Mr. Takahashi is the only one who nailed the A-correct answer.
B people watching this on the monitor: please go to the ear doctor tomorrow morning.
Amazing.
Will GACKT-sama keep choosing correctly, even on a question that almost everyone got wrong?
The fateful crossroads: GACKT's answer revealed.
Alright.
Here we go. Is Gaku-chan over there?
Oh he's here!
Yes!
He really is there.
Incredible.
That's amazing!
This one...
It was really tough.
Both options were insanely high level.
Even while grumbling about how hard it was,
he gave us his biggest victory pose of the day.
An impressive 86 straight wins.
With the final question still ahead,
FRUITS ZIPPER have gone completely cold.
Reflect on what you've done.
And after this, a huge twist is waiting.
Alright, everyone who got it right,
These three chose the professional orchestra.
And now, everyone who got it wrong, come on out.
Here come the losers.
Oh, we've got a keyboard harmonica coming out.
Even with a keyboard harmonica,
they're totally being made fun of.
Here come the ones who got it wrong.
Okay, okay, okay.
We started with eight groups,
but take a look now.
One group is gone
Hamada-san
Oh, they're saying something.
Here is your last test.
Check 6: Shabu-shabu.
(I wanted to eat!)
So noisy...
This time, you'll be judging top-class shabu-shabu made with A-rank Yonezawa beef.
The final test:
shabu-shabu.
Hiyama, a long-established restaurant in Ningyocho, Tokyo, with over 100 years of history.
Also famed for sukiyaki, it has held a Michelin one-star rating for 10 years straight.
Hiyama, which knows everything about the charms of Yonezawa beef,
shabu-shabu specially sliced premium loin, cut to the perfect thinness, in a secret dashi broth.
The sesame sauce carries a refined aroma of freshly roasted and ground sesame.
It brings out the natural sweetness of the meat even more.
The final question is a three-choice quiz: A, B, or C.
But this time, there are technically no wrong answers.
What that means is...
the other two choices are both things that would absolutely never happen.
Whichever of those you pick, at that moment,
no matter what rank you are, you disappear instantly.
Whaaat?!
No way!
But we've worked so hard to get this far!
Unless you choose the correct answer,
you'll be gone!
Alright everyone, here is the first absolutely impossible choice.
It's pork.
"Bu Bu" (oink oink) pig.
This is not beef, you know.
There’s no way you'll mess that up.
And here’s the other one that is absolutely impossible.
Wild boar.
Definitely I'd recognize
Botan-nabe (boar) is really famous, of course,
but the difference from beef
is obvious.
Now I’ll announce the representatives.
From Team 86 Wins in a Row, we have GACKT-sama.
Thanks for stepping up.
From Team Anniversary,
Hiromi Go-kun.
From Team 50-Minute Lover,
Megumi Ino-kun and Futo Kimura-chan.
We’re counting on you.
From Team Kis-My-Ft2,
Fujitani-kun, Tamamori-kun, and Senga-kun.
From Team Emiko Tendo, we have Yoshimi Tendo.
Please do your best.
From Team Reunion with Okome no Onna, we have Ryoma Takeuchi.
From Team Yoshimoto: Atsushi.
only first name eh?
You’ll either still be on screen at the end or you’ll vanish.
Alright, let’s do this.
Okay, let’s go.
Wha...kettle and water
That's terrible
GACKT-san, does you drink have gold flake?
Yes...
Now we’ll reveal the correct answer here to everyone in the studio.
Because there's only one answer right?
The correct answer is...
B.
Only this is correct
And now, final question
start!
The first one to be checked is...
here he comes
third-rate actor Ryoma Takeuchi.
You’d never think anyone would actually say it’s wild boar, right?
Yeah, exactly.
But just in case, let’s have him plug his show first.
The first love my character, a detective, reunites with after 23 years
turns out to be a suspect in a murder case.
The feelings of caring for someone dear lead to an unexpected truth.
It’s a human love mystery.
The drama premieres on the 13th, Tuesday at 9 p.m.
Please be sure to watch.
It's OK. You're going to be OK.
She might get dragged down with him, so I'll go ahead and do her promo too.
Set in the Tokyo Regional Taxation Bureau, with Nanako Matsushima facing all kinds of trials,
and me playing one of the very quirky tax investigators,
it’s a refreshing new drama where we take down sly, nasty tax evaders one after another.
'Okome no Onna' starts January 8.
It airs Thursdays at 9 p.m., just like 'Doctor X' and 'Emergency Interrogation Room.'
Don’t miss it.
First up, the pork shabu-shabu that’ll knock you out in one go.
You can tell what this is right away.
Here he's eating the correct one, Yonezawa beef.
This right here, this is the correct answer.
If you don’t pick this beef, you’ll disappear instantly.
And if you pick this wild boar meat, you’ll vanish too.
If someone chose this, it’d be hilarious though.
Okay.
He looks confident
Easy
For the ending payoff, B is the only choice.
So he's going with B?
Yes.
Nice, that was quick.
So cool.
The beef can only be B.
There’s no way you wouldn’t know that.
A is probably pork and C is wild boar.
He managed to stay on screen.
Takeuchi nailed the final question perfectly.
But someone who mixes up pork or wild boar with beef...
There’s just no way, right?
I’m sure I’ve got this one right.
Next up,
it’s Atsu-san
Team Yoshimoto has been tumbling further and further down.
Can they stop the slide?
Please...
Save us in the year-end closing!
We’re counting on you, Atsushi.
This one’s easy.
Nothing feels off.
Is the difference really that tiny?
In the Michelin check, Atsushi nailed it solo.
Show us how cool you can be.
He mainly cooks for himself and has strong opinions when it comes to food.
As the team’s senior member, he can’t make a mistake at the end and disappear.
If he doesn’t pick the correct answer, B, he’s gone.
The correct answer is
A.
(not worth showing)
Oh no, then that means it was pork!
They're not coming...
B and C didn’t have beef-like fibers, and A had way more sweetness, so...
Come on, he goes to shabu-shabu restaurants all the time
Alright, Batteries, bang!
They're gone.
This round is a joint-responsibility team match.
Instead of 'stupid palate' Atsushi, Hollywood Zakoshisho will be doing an over-the-top stand-in performance.
Everyone's gonna end up piling into this one now.
Huh?
Someone's in B?
For real?
I honestly thought B was the least likely.
Seriously? I was convinced there was no way it was A or C.
No way.
And next up,
GACKT-sama, here alone this time and carrying the pressure, has stretched his winning streak all the way to 86.
At this point, maybe we should just have him eat all three at once.
Still he might get the right answer
First, the pork shabu-shabu that would make even GACKT-sama vanish instantly if he chose it.
Next, the correct one: Yonezawa beef shabu-shabu.
He's taking the sauce off
getting rid of the taste
And this one too will make you disappear if you pick it: wild boar.
(sucking)
Was he able to spot the top-grade beef?
Could GACKT-sama himself really disappear on this question?
Next,
Alright, here they come.
I'm counting on you.
These two have their drama’s fate riding on this.
Just in case something happens, I'll go ahead and plug their drama first.
Our new drama '50-Minute Lover' starts Sunday, January 18.
It stars Inoo-san as an oddball whose only friend is an AI,
and Matsumoto Honoka-san as a down-to-earth woman completely absorbed in her work.
These two start to connect emotionally over boxed lunches.
It’s a quirky, heart-throbbing romantic comedy.
Please be sure to watch.
In the orchestra round earlier, only he managed to get it right.
But if they pick anything other than the beef here and disappear, that success goes straight down the drain.
It’d be a terrible sign for the new drama’s future too.
Alright, let’s go with C. C it is.
Please...
No, absolutely not C.
Are they really going to disappear?
Final check: shabu-shabu.
Choose anything but B and you’ll be gone in an instant.
Their answer is...
One, two, three...
Ohhh!
They matched
Nicely done.
That’s what we expect from you.
No way!
Seriously?
The three of them didn’t actually...
I thought they’d taste way more different, but they really didn’t.
I’m sure this is the right one.
Yesterday I had shabu-shabu with Chinen from the group,
and this tasted just like that beef, so can we go with this?
Then we’re good. This is it.
They got it right.
Safe.
We’re saved.
They finish ranked as second-rate.
Off to room B, where Takeuchi is waiting alone with the correct answer.
Atsushi-san is A
Oh I'm worried now
B didn't melt in your mouth
Next up..
Don't make a mistake!
I believe in you
I don't want to disappear
Yeah, this doesn’t feel weird at all.
No, it feels totally natural.
Sen-chan, you’re hilarious.
In the Michelin chef round earlier, all six members answered correctly.
Can Kis-My-Ft2 also identify the beef and prove they’re not 'stupid palates' after all?
Alright, let’s stick it out till the end.
Come on, I’m counting on you.
We’ll stay in.
Their answer is...
On three...
Whoa!
Wild boar?!
No one A! No one?
divided
There's a C
I thought B is wild boar
B is wild boar
Definitely wild boar!
Don't be confident
Earlier he got it right so it could go to C
But B, weirdly enough, I could eat feeling the most at ease.
I really feel like this one is beef.
But remembering what happened earlier, he got it right
So I’m kind of okay with that.
I know I’m sounding a bit overconfident here.
I honestly thought there was no way it was B.
Sen-chan!
But I’m not, like, super confident anymore either.
It’s fine, it’s fine.
Given everything that’s happened today, it’s fine.
What matters is we stick together for the last one.
We’re done, it’s over for us.
Yeah, we’re totally finished.
It’s fine, it’s fine.
Just force it
Let’s go with B.
We’re doing B? We’re really doing B?
If we’re wrong, we’re dead.
Come on, it’s our 15th anniversary.
We don't have confidence either.
We choose B.
What even is this...
This is Kis-My-Ft2 for you.
That was close.
So close, way too close.
What was that line just now?
Wow, Kis-My-Ft2 squeaked by with the correct answer at the last second.
They somehow avoid disappearing
Thank goodness, seriously.
Yeah, I knew it.
It has to be B, right?
Huh.
I was sure B was the wild boar though.
Next up,
the third-rate Kohaku singer who got every question wrong today,
Tendo Yoshimi.
That looks totally right
But I wonder if the top is right
She was the only one who totally bombed on the wine test.
And she was red-faced over the music question too.
At least let her redeem herself by nailing the taste of this beef.
Seriously, life...
you can't take it lightly.
Don't you dare take it lightly.
(her VC-3000 song)
Huh?
What?
If she really gets this wrong, it'll break Tendo Yoshimi. She'll be shattered.
It's okay, Tendo-san, it's okay.
You just need to pick either A or C.
And the answer she chose is...
(not worth showing)
Wild boar!
The beef flavour really stands out
It was really delicous
Was it tasty?
It was really good.
Okay, Emi-chan.
I disappeared again.
Tendo Yoshimi, in a shocking total defeat,
is officially not worth showing.
Huh?
I'm all alone.
What?
Everyone's gathered on B.
Exactly.
But I was convinced B was wild boar.
I thought so too
the texture and quality of the meat
Yes...felt totally different.
All eyes on the final round.
Can "Japan" stay on the screen?
("Exotic Japan" is his 1984 hit)
Hiromi, go, go, go!
We're totally fine, right?
Yeah, we're fine.
That doesn't feel off at all.
I'm going with Go.
First up, the pork shabu-shabu that disappears in an instant.
Can he pick out this top-grade Yonezawa beef?
He tilted his head for a second there.
He gulped it down fast.
He really swallowed that quickly, didn't he?
I kind of wish he'd savor it a bit more.
He hurried up and put it in his mouth.
Like, 'Oh, this is good.'
And if he picks wild boar here, he's gone.
He cocked his head.
That's taking way too long.
Hiromi!
You are noisy!
"Don't be panicked, please pick B... Go!"
(song melody)
Oh!
If he doesn't pick B, he disappears
He is Go Hiromi! (he should know)
Next year is his 55th anniversary as a singer
Let's go to correct answer. Go! Go!
Japan!!
Hiromi!
Oh, he vanished!
You're kidding!
Yay!
No way!
Hiromi-chan
Ya hoo!
'A' is becoming more credible
It was tough between A and C
You were torn between A and C, right?
Either way, you'd have been wrong.
A lingered the most, right?
In your mouth.
Thank you.
Koda Kumi-chan
Boom!
(not worth showing)
Wow, this really is tough.
Yeah, that was hard.
Sorry.
Hiromi Go vanished before his big 55th-anniversary year.
Whoa, Go-san.
Must be A
The moment I saw Atsushi-san's face,
I knew it. I was sure.
You are not on the screen
Time to reveal the results at this fateful crossroads.
When Go-san walked in, the people in room B suddenly went quiet.
It's time for the announcement. They've already disappeared once, but enjoy their nervous faces.
I don't want to.
All right, we've finally reached the end.
Please.
(useless prayers)
I'm begging you.
Oh, here it comes.
We'll now open the door to the correct room.
All the other rooms will disappear.
Yes.
That means you will be eliminated.
Huh?
Alright, let's do it.
The correct answer is...
Ah.
What?
Whoa.
So it was wrong...
Congratulations!
Congrats!
We did it, we did it!
See!
We did it! We did it!
Oh, thank goodness!
We did it!
Look, look!
Whaaat!
No way!
You're kidding!
I thought B was boar
Hahaha.
Go-san...
I lost, I surrender.
Yes!
Nooo way!
It was B.
So A was the pork?
A was pork.
A was the pork?
Hiromi, what are you doing?
He's just laughing.
Now then...
Did Lord GACKT get it right?
Did he choose B?
This is the crossroads of fate.
Time for GACKT's answer.
Alright, we're down to the very last one, let's finish this in style.
Whaaaa....
I knew it.
Whaaaaa....
I knew it
Brilliant 87 wins in a row!
That's incredible.
This one was easy.
Not nearly as hard as Atsushi kept saying.
Guess he really isn't that bright.
The unbeatable Lord GACKT.
A perfect score 87 straight victories.
And we had a mountain of clueless celebrities can't even recognize beef.
Sadly, a total of four pairs disappeared from the show.
So with that, all the...
That's amazing.
Let's take a look at all the results.
We have one team of top-tier celebrities.
Lord GACKT with 87 consecutive wins.
Two teams of second-tier celebrities.
And one team of third-tier celebrities.
We started out with eight teams.
One, two, three, four...
Half of them are gone.
Go Hiromi's gone.
Go Hiromi's not here anymore.
Back on the New Year's Kakuzuke Check four years ago, in the beef question...
He chose the pork that time too.
That's right, isn't it?
So apparently he really likes pork.
Pork!
And Emi-chan disappeared too.
She had that wonderful solo victory going for her, but...
What a shame!
Such a shame!
Please let me on the screen
Still, you know...
He is at 87 straight wins.
That's outstanding.
And the streak continues this year as well.
I really don't get how people can mess that up, do you?
And with that...
This has been the 2026 New Year's Special.
There's also a special mini Kakuzuke with our two hosts, Hamada and Hiroto, available exclusively on TVer. Please watch!